<wp:post_name><![CDATA[fairhope-catalyst-a-dirty-little-secret]]>
</wp:post_name>Good enuf for vestavia.
<wp:post_name><![CDATA[hell-yea]]>
</wp:post_name>
<wp:post_name><![CDATA[catalyst-panic-and-confusion]]>
</wp:post_name>			
Your special election for the Council-Manager form of government scheduled on 10/2 will NOW be delayed until the general election on 11/6. This is a decision which will be announced directly from the Judge of Probate’s office and I will share more details when these become available.<wp:post_name><![CDATA[fairhope-council-shows-its-colors]]>
</wp:post_name>		Baby Boone is a mere front man of us.  We are SPARTICUS.   We represent every sitting judge in the county.  We own over half of the county commission.   We control  the majority of the city councils.   
<wp:post_name><![CDATA[bury-the-body]]>
</wp:post_name>
<wp:post_name><![CDATA[crystal-ball]]>
</wp:post_name>		
They are not called good ole boys for nothing. Catalyst has a strong throat hold on Baldwin County and they want Fairhope back in their pocket.This is business as usual in Baldwin County. Elected officials ignore any conflicts of interest and to recuse one self from any conflicts of interest is unheard of.Fairhope has a chance to break the cycle of at large council’s, that are often Catalyst slate candidates, such as the current council.<wp:post_name><![CDATA[raising-eyebrows]]>
</wp:post_name>		Comforter of the afflicted
<wp:post_name><![CDATA[insanity]]>
</wp:post_name>	<item>
Several of you have asked about rumors you've heard since the election day was pushed back to November 6th, so let's set the record straight and allow you to speak against these scare tactics with confidence.<strong>1. The Mayor is going to appoint one of her friends to be City Manager.</strong>False! This rumor is the one most often reported to me, but it's false in so many ways it's hard to begin. First of all, if the Referendum passes on November 6th, nothing changes with our City government until the Mayor and Council Members are elected (or re-elected) in the Fall of 2020 on the normal 4-year municipal election cycle. Secondly, in 2020 the new Council will have five members (Mayor plus four other Council members) and no one Member - even the Mayor - has the individual power to appoint or hire anyone, much less the City Manager. Only a majority of Council acting at a Public Meeting will be able to hire (or fire) the City Manager. And thirdly, the City Manager will be a qualified professional with an appropriate college degree(s) and lots of experience.<strong>2. The Justice Department or the Probate Court will set the boundaries of the three election districts in Fairhope.</strong>False! Alabama law is very clear that the current City Council, acting in Public Meetings, must set the boundaries of the three districts, and the districts must be of equal size by population.<strong>3. Once a City Manager is hired, the Council will have little control over the Manager's activities, and it will be next to impossible to discipline or terminate the City Manager.</strong>False! By law the City Council will always be the ultimate authority in Fairhope and no employee including the City Manager is outside of the control of the Council. The City Council hires, disciplines, and fires the City Manager at its will. It's the City Council that will set the parameters of the City Manager's employment contract, so there will be no surprises.<strong>4. The City Manager will cost too much money.</strong>False! The City Manager will be paid about 15-20% more than the average salaries of the top Department Heads, which is a normal practice. If you review the benefits we have previously cited for having a City Manager (such as fewer lawsuits, better employee morale, improvements in City infrastructure, creation of strategic planning, elimination of redundancy in City staff, and so forth) the real truth is that we can't afford not to have a City Manager.<strong>5. A District Council Member will control City activities inside his/her district, and that Member will be have veto power over City projects inside the district.</strong>False! You may have read about that kind of practice in large cities like Chicago and New York City, but Alabama law is very clear that the District Plan to be implemented in Fairhope does not permit individual Council Members, including the Mayor, to wield that kind of power. The Council may only act as a group, in public meetings, and then only by a majority of votes. And no one Member can interfere with the City Manager's oversight and direction of the City workforce, under penalty of law.<strong>6. The two At-Large members will likely join forces with one of the district members to work against the interests of the other two districts.</strong>False! As you recall, the new Council in 2020 will consist of the Mayor and one Council Member both elected At-Large, plus three other Members each elected from one of three districts. The reason this rumor is false is that the two At-Large Members would be committing political suicide to create an on-going conspiracy of control with one district Member -- for the simple reason that 2/3 of the voters who vote for the At-Large Members would toss the bums out at the next election. It just makes no sense that the At-Large Members would ignore the concerns and needs of a vast majority of the voters.<strong>7. Voters already have access to all of the elected officials, they don't need a better system of representation.</strong>False! Which one of the five At-Large Council Members is watching out for the special concerns of the residents along US 98 north of 104 when issues like water pressure and large apartment complexes come up? Which one of the five At-Large Council Members is watching out for the special concerns of the residents east of US 98 especially along the 13 and 181 corridors when issues like growth management, zoning, and storm water management come up? And which one of the five At-Large Council Members is watching out for the special concerns of the residents in the new housing developments south of the High School when those same issues and concerns come up in their area?<strong>*** Please let me know if you hear any more rumors so we can promptly confront them, thanks. ***</strong>Please contribute if you can...Thanks again to all of you who contributed money several weeks ago to the FSF 2018 fund in support of Fresh Start Fairhope. Most of that money was spent on advertising activities in anticipation of the election being held October 2nd, so our current fund balance is not enough to re-send our message to the voters before the new election date of November 6th.Looking ahead, we have created our promotional strategy for the four weeks remaining until the revised election day, November 6th. This plan requires a budget slightly larger than what we spent in advance of the October 2nd non-election, so we need another round of fundraising.Why spend money again? There are two reasons. Firstly, the opposition has had more time to prepare and put its own messaging out to the voters, and we must overcome that. Secondly, we have to present a more complicated set of facts than before, because the AG Opinion forces us to explain the District plan plus our own original message about the Council-Manager system. We are working on "content" right now, and we must have our fact-based arguments in a clear, concise format when we execute the meetings, social media advertising, and mailers we are planning. None of this can be left to the last minute, but getting out our complete message depends heavily on successful fundraising over the next 5-10 days. {From Fresh Start Fairhope}<wp:post_name><![CDATA[yes]]>
</wp:post_name>
<wp:post_name><![CDATA[loser]]>
</wp:post_name>
<wp:post_name><![CDATA[fairhope-change-of-government]]>
</wp:post_name>
<wp:post_name><![CDATA[women-of-baldwin]]>
</wp:post_name>
<wp:post_name><![CDATA[special-interest]]>
</wp:post_name>			Yeah, right “Bring Christian ethics to Montgomery.”  Like he is the ONLY one to do it.		
<wp:post_name><![CDATA[people-power-wake-up-gulf-shores]]>
</wp:post_name>			
36 West Liberty St.<wp:post_name><![CDATA[chuckee-cheeze]]>
</wp:post_name>
You have an option:<wp:post_name><![CDATA[halloween-characters]]>
</wp:post_name>	I do know a lot of truth. Some of it relevant, some not. Some of it I will express in this rebuttal, some I will keep quiet about. 
<wp:post_name><![CDATA[the-face-of-no]]>
</wp:post_name>	
<wp:post_name><![CDATA[fear]]>
</wp:post_name>		Vote YES.
just how corrupt the system is:<wp:post_name><![CDATA[you-win-some-you-lose-some]]>
</wp:post_name><item>
<wp:post_name><![CDATA[blind-voting-straight-ticket]]>
</wp:post_name>			I see your point in lamenting on the blind straight ticket voting.  But the only other option is to vote Democrat and the Democrats are just too liberal for the "typical" Baldwin County voter.  When the typical Baldwin County voter sees a Democrat on the ballot, all he or she can think of is Pelosi, Schumer, and Anifa.
<wp:post_name><![CDATA[50-years-ago]]>
</wp:post_name>		
<wp:post_name><![CDATA[ignorance-is-bliss]]>
</wp:post_name>	A. There’s absolutely no need to change a successful method of governance because of recent issues with elected personnel. Fairhope has been here longer than any of us and will continue beyond our lifetimes, so making fundamental changes should be well thought out, clearly communicated, and follow state statutes. It is my opinion that this referendum failed on all three points. 
<wp:post_name><![CDATA[happy-thanksgiving-3]]>
</wp:post_name>
<wp:post_name><![CDATA[no-guardrails]]>
</wp:post_name>
<wp:post_name><![CDATA[catalyst]]>
</wp:post_name>	wp:meta_value><![CDATA[3795]]></wp:meta_value>
I know this because they fund the campaigns of the politicians and the politicians pay Catalyst.
Please read carefully the article and think of all the implications, quid pro quo’s, dark money and in your face corruption, that originated in the Governor's office and trickled down through the ranks. Political positions passed out, like candy on Halloween, to cover up crimes of the past administration.Where are the checks and balances? How do we hold elected officials accountable when those charged with that task appear to be equally corrupt?2019 looks like Alabama may become even more corrupt. That is what you can expect when 65%, of the 33% voting, vote a “Blind Vote” or straight ticket vote.<wp:post_name><![CDATA[barstool]]>
</wp:post_name>
<wp:post_name><![CDATA[russian-roulette-fairhope-style]]>
</wp:post_name>		
<wp:post_name><![CDATA[daphne-decision]]>
</wp:post_name><wp:meta_key><![CDATA[classic-editor-remember]]></wp:meta_key><wp:meta_value><![CDATA[classic-editor]]></wp:meta_value>
		Who is surprised that the Daphne Council, controlled by Catalyst, will pick Armstrong?
The council cannot figure out how to make something legal that has been going on illegally for over 10 years. The opposition, mostly Baptist, and a minority are scared Fairhope Ave will be renamed Bourbon Street. They vote Catalyst. Let’s see what’s happens!<wp:post_name><![CDATA[chasing-your-tail]]>
</wp:post_name>
<wp:post_name><![CDATA[run-away-train]]>
</wp:post_name>			When I make enough money I am moving to another area.  I don’t want to stay in Baldwin County after they are through with it
<wp:post_name><![CDATA[in-the-dark]]>
</wp:post_name>		Let's shine the brightest light on catalyst in 2019. They are Fairhopers biggest enemy.
.entry-header {font-family: 'Shadows Into Light', cursive !important;}</style><wp:post_name><![CDATA[kindness]]>
</wp:post_name>
<wp:post_name><![CDATA[happy-new-year-2]]>
</wp:post_name>
<wp:post_name><![CDATA[exposure-2]]>
</wp:post_name>
<wp:post_name><![CDATA[congratulations-fairhope]]>
</wp:post_name>	Jubilee!!!
<wp:post_name><![CDATA[consequences]]>
</wp:post_name>			Which was built by bp money.Should be fun. I'm sure the Ripp Report will provide the fireworks.
Have no fear Fairhope, the people involved with, You Don’t Know Jack, are now going to set the rules for everyone else. Council President Burrell, the City liaison on the board, showed up late, without pen, paper or notes, which he had to borrow, but he let Airport Authority Chairman Joe McEnerney know who was Captain.Captain Jack blasted Joe at about minute 14:00. Seems Joe, who is the Chairman of the Board, was guaranteeing certain "chosen ones" hanger locations, prior to any bid process. Joe even gave the Ripp Report a shout out at the end of the meeting.Captain Jack has made it perfectly clear from his past actions that no one gets a hanger location without Captain Jack’s approval. He should not hold the title of city liaison, he has not represented the citizens or the best interests of the community.As President of the Council, he has run the Airport Authority to the satisfaction of the 1%, or less, that use the Airport. Captain Jack was also the man who made sure the City Attorney and Municipal Judge appointments went as he wished. Hopefully all three will leave their posts in the next election.Captain Jack has dominated the position of Council President, going on 7 years. The Council has learned what Joe has not, that is, Captain Jack is flying the plane, they are only passengers.<wp:post_name><![CDATA[captain-jack]]>
</wp:post_name>	
<wp:post_name><![CDATA[shovel-ready]]>
</wp:post_name>			Progress in the name of Jesus.
<wp:post_name><![CDATA[boiling-frog]]>
</wp:post_name>
<wp:post_name><![CDATA[tick-tock]]>
</wp:post_name>
<wp:post_name><![CDATA[state-of-the-city-2019]]>
</wp:post_name>	
<wp:post_name><![CDATA[stepping-up]]>
</wp:post_name>
<wp:post_name><![CDATA[knock-on-doors]]>
</wp:post_name><wp:meta_key><![CDATA[email]]></wp:meta_key><wp:meta_key><![CDATA[comment]]></wp:meta_key><wp:meta_value><![CDATA[0]]></wp:meta_value>
<wp:meta_key><![CDATA[options]]></wp:meta_key><wp:meta_value><![CDATA[0]]></wp:meta_value>

<wp:post_name><![CDATA[communication]]>
</wp:post_name>		Keep exposing the fools.		And that council, I understand that the truth does come out in the end for everyone. There are always a set of eyes in a dark corner of the bar or street corner watching.... waiting! 
<wp:post_name><![CDATA[the-good-the-bad-and-the-ugly]]>
</wp:post_name>
<wp:post_name><![CDATA[nothing-is-free]]>
</wp:post_name>Claims to be Christian!!
The council continues to find itself embroiled in one controversy after another. The council has no leadership! The four other councilmen have given Captain Jack full rein to drag them through the mud with him. Catalyst will be their undoing.<wp:post_name><![CDATA[jack-gets-an-f-again]]>
</wp:post_name>
Citizens of Fairhope get ready because another subject, dear to all our hearts, is going to be the focus of the council, education and our schools. I predict the council will, again, elect to shelter themselves from any decision and relegate that responsibility to anyone other than themselves. They care about one thing and one thing only, returning to the good ole days of Can’t.<wp:post_name><![CDATA[pedaling-backwards]]>
</wp:post_name>
<wp:post_name><![CDATA[gold-star-2]]>
</wp:post_name>		Elliot cites the reason is that people living outside the city limits are being told what to do by elected officials they did not vote for
<wp:post_name><![CDATA[faux-tax-gas-tax]]>
</wp:post_name>
<wp:post_name><![CDATA[goat-hill-piggy-bank]]>
</wp:post_name><wp:meta_key><![CDATA[email]]></wp:meta_key><wp:meta_key><![CDATA[comment]]></wp:meta_key><wp:meta_value><![CDATA[0]]></wp:meta_value>
<wp:meta_key><![CDATA[options]]></wp:meta_key><wp:meta_value><![CDATA[0]]></wp:meta_value>

<wp:post_name><![CDATA[captain-jack-at-the-controls]]>
</wp:post_name>
<wp:post_name><![CDATA[laugh-out-loud-baldwin]]>
</wp:post_name>
President of the Fairhope Council famously said he was tired of hearing from the citizens, citizens, citizens. The CITIZENS better be sure Burrell gets the message.<wp:post_name><![CDATA[community-engagement]]>
</wp:post_name>		
<wp:post_name><![CDATA[shut-up-2]]>
</wp:post_name>
BUT:This week I am exploring my old stomping grounds of Belize, The out islands and Guatemala. I will be back next week, maybe.In the mean time you may wish to read a past post that is going to affect everyone who drives through the Parker Road/Highway 98 intersection.<wp:post_name><![CDATA[vacation-time]]>
</wp:post_name>		Next election we MUST inform the voters of this outfit and who they have put in office so we can get them out of office
<wp:post_name><![CDATA[legal-corruption]]>
</wp:post_name>
<wp:post_name><![CDATA[liar-liar-pants-on-fire]]>
</wp:post_name>	Watch Gringo: the Dangerous Life of John McAfee.
<wp:post_name><![CDATA[one-woman]]>
</wp:post_name>
In what was considered a political move by those attending,100 plus, the good Judge wanted to turn a family friendly organization into her own selected Board and exclude those serving. The Judge was knocked off her broomstick when people started booing her and then was soundly defeated by a 75% margin vote. This is a great organization and for one I am glad it did not get hijacked.<wp:post_name><![CDATA[fairhope-2020]]>
</wp:post_name><item>
<wp:post_name><![CDATA[what-education-lottery]]>
</wp:post_name>			Alabama's unemployment is three percent.
<wp:post_name><![CDATA[one-woman-2]]>
</wp:post_name>
<wp:post_name><![CDATA[dirty-hands]]>
</wp:post_name>		
“Why senators like Marsh and Albritton continue to do PCI’s bidding even after they called the state their deadliest enemies is a mystery.”The tribe admits the state was played, that they plan to expand their empire and will not pay taxes. It seems some have not only ignored Trump’s warning but the one that PCI has stated about itself.Alabama is going to lose BILLIONS, with the political lottery, and at the same time will ensure Poarch Creek Indians a gaming monopoly.<wp:post_name><![CDATA[portables-and-prisons]]>
</wp:post_name>
Did you notice in the Mayor’s statement about the forecast that the city could be debt free in June 2019, next month? That is the Mayor and her staff’s accomplishment not the Council who has fought the present administration at every turn.The Catalyst Council is fully responsible for the Apartments at Fly Creek, the Mayor opposed the project. When they open, Fairhope will feel the negative impact of a good ole boy deal supported by the Council.The Mayor had a plan for education that was immediate and required no taxes. The Council plan is a self imposed 3 mil tax.<wp:post_name><![CDATA[dog-and-pony-show]]>
</wp:post_name>
<wp:post_name><![CDATA[dog-and-pony-show-2]]>
</wp:post_name>wp:meta_value><![CDATA[375]]></wp:meta_value>

<wp:post_name><![CDATA[alabama-national-news]]>
</wp:post_name>		The politicians just want this to go to the Supreme Court.    There are other issues besides this exercise in baiting the radicals on BOTH sides.    Geez, even the nicest and rape clauses were removed from this bill by my fellow stupid white men who give the rest of us white guys a bad name.  
<wp:post_name><![CDATA[tax-tax-and-re-tax]]>
</wp:post_name><wp:meta_key><![CDATA[email]]></wp:meta_key><wp:meta_key><![CDATA[comment]]></wp:meta_key><wp:meta_value><![CDATA[0]]></wp:meta_value>
<wp:meta_key><![CDATA[options]]></wp:meta_key><wp:meta_value><![CDATA[0]]></wp:meta_value>

<wp:post_name><![CDATA[equal-representation]]>
</wp:post_name>		Real leader.Like Trump:
<wp:post_name><![CDATA[memorial-day-2]]>
</wp:post_name>	Honor and remember dead servicemen and womenVeteran's Day
Gulf Shores, just like Fairhope underestimated the citizens frustration and the condescending way those opposed to the apartments were treated. It’s official, a law suit has been filed. A special recognition goes to Pete Sims of Gulf Shores and his perseverance in representing the citizens impacted negatively by the Apartments.<wp:post_name><![CDATA[gulf-shores-lawsuit-2020]]>
</wp:post_name>
<wp:post_name><![CDATA[three-strikes]]>
</wp:post_name>		
<wp:post_name><![CDATA[alabama-first-in-political-corruption]]>
</wp:post_name>		Do you know how much it costs to run a campaign?   Do you know how little politicians make?  Do you know how many hours a week they spend on the job?   Something has to make it worth their while This guy will too.<wp:post_name><![CDATA[loss-of-a-friend]]>
</wp:post_name>
<wp:post_name><![CDATA[disposal]]>
</wp:post_name>			
<wp:post_name><![CDATA[deliberate-distortion-or-twisting-of-meaning]]>
</wp:post_name>			Drop a gum wrapper on the street and you will get fined by the city but the  city can dump hundreds of gallons in the bay	
<wp:post_name><![CDATA[fairhope-petition]]>
</wp:post_name>Diana Brewer lost her City Council seat because she was selling the Fly Creek Apartments for her 'patron' Corte. She was correctly voted off of the CC because she was a traitor to Fairhope.  Good riddance to her.   Then she moved to a marketing management position at something in Mobile (some type of museum) that quickly shut down due to lack of interest (not good at her job?).   Interestingly, she then shows up with a great position at Weeks Bay, which has puzzled me from the get-go.  Why is this loser marketable anyplace?   No one likes her other than Jack Burrell and Corte;  and then it hit me.    Did Corte fund this position?   Burrell &amp; Brewer were best buddies on the Council a few years ago so they can still work together for Corte's interests?    Now, here we are:  Jack Burrell is trying to place the triangle property into Weeks Bay Conservancy........what a coup that might be for the 3 of them.  Other CC members remain silent, city attorney remains silent....in a few years Weeks Bay changes its course and, suddenly, condos and apartments abound on the triangle.Nobody gives a #uck.You nailed it.  You called it.  You see the council’s moves.
<wp:post_name><![CDATA[baldwin-county-municipal-alert-municipal-conservation-easement]]>
</wp:post_name>
<wp:post_name><![CDATA[passport-to-paris]]>
</wp:post_name>
<wp:post_name><![CDATA[happy-july-4th]]>
</wp:post_name>		THAT TO ENSURE THESE RIGHTS GOVERNMENTS ARE INSTITUTED AMONG MEN DERIVING TGEIR POWER BY THE SELF GOVERNED
Please sign the petition:Over 600 have signed, help us reach a 1000<wp:post_name><![CDATA[gold-mine-for-sale]]>
</wp:post_name>			
<wp:post_name><![CDATA[the-jester]]>
</wp:post_name>
<wp:meta_value><![CDATA[3797]]></wp:meta_value>

<wp:post_name><![CDATA[taxes-tolls-and-schools]]>
</wp:post_name>
<wp:post_name><![CDATA[mega-mistake]]>
</wp:post_name>
<wp:post_name><![CDATA[fact-hardest-working-elected-city-official-eastern-shore-fairhope-mayor-karin-wilson]]>
</wp:post_name>The council has allowed so much growth that it has stressed the sewers.  The council doesn’t care because they do what Truland and DR Horton tell them what to do
<wp:post_name><![CDATA[lagniappe]]>
</wp:post_name>
<wp:post_name><![CDATA[for-the-record-mega-money]]>
</wp:post_name>		
<wp:post_name><![CDATA[fairhope-sewer-backstory]]>
</wp:post_name>
CC: Mobile Baykeeper Board of Directors<wp:post_name><![CDATA[letter-of-concern]]>
</wp:post_name>
<wp:post_name><![CDATA[timeline]]>
</wp:post_name>
<wp:post_name><![CDATA[in-the-same-boat]]>
</wp:post_name>
State Senator Chris Elliott (R - Daphne ) said the meeting should be moved, not the people. Easy to say, now let’s see if Elliott follows up. The meeting should be held in Mobile or Baldwin County.Fairhope Mayor Wilson said it best:Mayor Karin Wilson of Fairhope, AlabamaJuly 30 at 10:06 PM ·My Thoughts on the Proposed Toll for the Long-Awaited New Bridge:I’m 100% against a toll to build this bridge whatever the fee.The State should have invested the billion+ dollar BP settlement into the two counties that suffered the most instead of taking this money for its own operating budget. Why punish the tourists and hardworking citizens of Mobile and Baldwin County to make up the shortfall due to poor planning and budgeting? We’re the ones paying the most to the State in tourism dollars. How would a toll impact this important revenue stream?The critical need for a new bridge has been discussed for over a decade. To react as though building it now is an overnight emergency is absurd. It’s the perfect example of government getting away with zero accountability.A household or business cannot operate with the idea that if we cannot balance our budget we can force someone else to pay for it. We must budget within our means or fail and suffer the consequences. It's a pretty good incentive having to be accountable.As Mayor, I tackled the City budget the same way I do my business or household budget. Before I took office, the City was relying on half of Utility’s profits (almost $6M annually) to balance its budget. In a few short years, after cutting wasteful spending and investing in ways to become more productive and efficient, both budgets significantly improved.The City is now self-sustaining and has paid off all its debt. Our Utility Department can use all of its profitable finally to invest in long overdue infrastructure needs.Proposing a toll due to lack of strategic planning and budgeting is not the answer.The State of Alabama stole and misused the money from BP. They used the money to cover up all the Goat Hill mistakes, built a Hotel and refurbished the Governor’s Beach House. State Senator Pittman, as appointed BP trustee, secured $750,000.00 in BP money, for his “tractor” company. Now Governor Poison Ivy wants to put the burden of the bridge on the backs of those who had BP money squandered by the state.Many proposals have been mentioned to reduce the tolls or eliminate them. So here is another suggestion, A, wait until after the 2020 elections. B, increase contract to 60 years. C, Baldwin and Mobile residents will get a pass stamp on their tags, no toll. If C fails then go for a 25% toll, for Baldwin and Mobile County residents, on the retail price. $6.00 toll would be $1.50.If all this fails then vote their sorry asses out of office and cover Goat Hill with calamine lotion.<wp:post_name><![CDATA[poison-ivy-bridge]]>
</wp:post_name>
<wp:post_name><![CDATA[straw-man]]>
</wp:post_name>
<wp:meta_value><![CDATA[https://cdn.rippreport.com/wp-content/uploads/2019/09/dorsey-fairhope-2.jpg]]></wp:meta_value>
<wp:meta_value><![CDATA[STRAW MAN &#x2d; WONDERFUL WEDNESDAY]]></wp:meta_value>
Seriously, if you keep exposing these crooks for what they really are then you may be putting yourself in danger.   You are getting in between   these  greedy lying crooks and their money	
<wp:post_name><![CDATA[puzzle-pieces]]>
</wp:post_name>	Ofcourse we could have just had congress appropriate the funds from the budget, right? I mean big government deficits were the way of the land under the Obama Administration, Right? 
Baldwin County citizens need to learn from this experience.<wp:post_name><![CDATA[fingerprint]]>
</wp:post_name>		
<wp:post_name><![CDATA[rsa-%e2%81%a0-no-gas-for-point-clear-or-tourism]]>
</wp:post_name>			So you folks in Baldwin need a bridge to get to Mobile?  The state will put a toll on it.  It was this topic you started waking up and took a stand
<wp:post_name><![CDATA[ripp-report-podcast]]>
</wp:post_name>
<div id=at_zurlpreview>“And in case anyone tries to tell you “it’s all City money”, know that is not true. The City operates with tax dollars. The Utility Department operates with rate fees. The money is not the same and going back to the old way of doing business should never happen again. ““We have much more to cover during September and I have implored Council to take the time needed to meet and ensure the budget passes on time this year. All amendments to the proposed budget must take place with communication in open meetings for the benefit of citizens, employees and me. This is how all government budgets are developed. Council has avoided this open process the last three budget cycle and it is contrary to State Statute.”This process before has enabled Council to sit on the budget for many months beyond the deadline without any accountability and prevented the ability of employees and I to do our job successfully. Please help us hold them accountable. With Council’s willingness to pass the budget by the 10/1 deadline, we can make 2020 a model year for our citizens.Sincerely,Mayor Karin WilsonCity of Fairhope, Office: 251.990.0110, Cell: 251.422.0669, Karin.Wilson@FairhopeAL.gov, www.mayorkarinwilson.com 2019 State of the City, Future Fairhope: Moving Forward Together<wp:post_name><![CDATA[transparency]]>
</wp:post_name>
Exposure and the Court of Public Opinion will lead to the council’s removal in 2020. Monday night Fairhope City Council will vote themselves a free health insurance coverage. Additional they will set the Mayor’s salary, ignoring an Auburn Study, that was suppose to give guidance to these issues.If you live in Fairhope please attend the City Council Meeting Sept. 9, see for yourself, what has become obvious to many, Fairhope Council is totally out of touch with their constituency.Backstory Podcast is a production of Backwoods Media, LLC an Alabama Domestic Limited Liability Company located in Baldwin County, Alabama. The regular participants are Francis Paul Ripp, U.S.M.C. combat veteran, of the Ripp Report (www.rippreport.com) non-profit/ consumer advocacy organization;Facebook pages The Ripp Report and Baldwin County Legal Eagle. The Backwoods Southern Lawyer: Harry Still, III a former ICMA Credentialed Manger, Economic Developer, City Planner and County Manager currently an attorney in private practice;<wp:post_name><![CDATA[backstory-podcast]]>
</wp:post_name>
</a><wp:post_name><![CDATA[baldwin-county-sewer-regulation-a-litmus-test]]>
</wp:post_name>
<wp:post_name><![CDATA[down-home-fairhope-jester]]>
</wp:post_name>Brown snags Arts Center contract.
The Jester, Burrell and Boone do not know what Transparency, Accountability, Ethics or what constitutes a Conflict of interest. I promised that I would follow through on a complaint against Councilman Robert Brown this week.Councilman Brown and his business partner Cliff Pitman are making a mockery of Ethical Conduct. Sure some of the sneaky self serving things they are doing may not be criminal but the lack of Ethics stains Fairhope and the Citizens of the Community.The Citizens of Fairhope have to stand up to the Jester and his demented view of right and wrong. Three of the Council, Burrell Boone and especially Brown, have used their elected position for personal gain. I will repeat, it may not be criminal, in some instances, but it defies all standards of honest GovernmentThis last Monday, September 16, 2019 I personally delivered a complaint against Councilman Robert Brown to the Alabama Attorney General, White Collar Crime Division, Special Prosecutors. The complaint letter was accompanied by a 42 page booklet of supporting, and related, documents.What will the Attorney General do? I do not know, however you as citizens should have enough common sense to see through the Jester’s Bull Sh-- interpretation of “transparency”.[embeddoc url="https://cdn.rippreport.com/Doc-Sep-18-2019-18_131_compressed.pdf" download="all"]<wp:post_name><![CDATA[blind-leading-the-blind]]>
</wp:post_name>
<wp:meta_value><![CDATA[https://cdn.rippreport.com/wp-content/uploads/2019/09/cropped-robert-brown-facebook.jpg]]></wp:meta_value>

<wp:post_name><![CDATA[crazy]]>
</wp:post_name>
<wp:meta_value><![CDATA[https://cdn.rippreport.com/wp-content/uploads/2019/09/cropped-hoss-mack.jpg]]></wp:meta_value>
Sort of like the politicians in Baldwin County...
<wp:post_name><![CDATA[documents]]>
</wp:post_name>	wp:meta_value><![CDATA[https://cdn.rippreport.com/wp-content/uploads/2019/09/cropped-documents-fb.png]]></wp:meta_value>
<wp:meta_value><![CDATA[DOCUMENTS &#x2d; THE RIPP REPORT &#x2d; WONDERFUL WEDNESDAY]]></wp:meta_value>
		The lying, theiving, deceiving clown from your hometown.
From ourselves.<wp:post_name><![CDATA[backstory-podcast-4]]>
</wp:post_name>	wp:meta_value><![CDATA[BACKSTORY PODCAST #4]]></wp:meta_value>
<wp:meta_value><![CDATA[Backstory Podcast Number 4]]></wp:meta_value>

<wp:post_name><![CDATA[quid-quo-pro]]>
</wp:post_name>wp:meta_value><![CDATA[https://cdn.rippreport.com/wp-content/uploads/2019/10/cropped-handshake.jpg]]></wp:meta_value>
<wp:meta_value><![CDATA[THE RIPP REPORT &#x2d; QUID PRO QUO]]></wp:meta_value>
<wp:meta_value><![CDATA[Please read the Mayor’s comments and file written complaints to those listed at the end of the article. Stop being silent gullible pawns of a council that does nothing for nothing and always does something for something.]]></wp:meta_value>

<wp:post_name><![CDATA[backstory-alabama-the-ripp-report-podcast-5]]>
</wp:post_name>On May 29th council meeting the Mayor of Fairhope begged the council to reconsider two issues on the agenda. One, the conservation easement involving the triangle property, 102 acres worth 20 million, that the council was willing to give away while at the same time proposing to buy 2.6 million of property on hwy.13. Fairhope paid 8.25 million in a lawsuit plus 3 million in attorney fees as a SETTLEMENT for the property. Burrell and Boone supported the lawsuit that they LOST.Second was an appraisal for property for recreation land on hwy. 13. At that May meeting, and the work session, Mr Burrell said it was for an appraisal only, not a purchase.Watch the first hour and tell me who is representing the citizens? The Mayor made her position very clear as well as many citizens. The council proceeded with the appraisal and was deaf to any comment.They failed on the conservation easement, but be prepared for them to try again to give away city property.https://www.youtube.com/watch?v=O4Lv316ByaI&t=4332sFast forward to September and the council, the 3 b’s, without any public participation or any plan to pay for 2.6 million in property, passed a resolution to purchase the property, despite a very questionable appraisal. It is the ultimate lie. The B’s say it was discussed and it was, between the council members and the Rec. board. The citizens were denied any public comment.The Council has been found guilty, in Federal Court, for violating the Constitution of the United States, the right of free speech.
Last week in a city council work session, the Mayor was discussing the free family insurance, around 17,000 thousand dollars for each part time councilman, no city employees have such insurance. Council President Burrell the most prolific honey bee, threatened the Mayor with arrest, if she did not “shut up”. The Mayor was representing the citizens.The council has lost in Federal Court, threatened to throw the Mayor in jail, for representing the citizens, and has denied citizens comment on the recreation property. This is just a snapshot of their dismal record. The Council did pass a law that prevented anyone from sleeping in their car and forbid feeding the geese.Tonight the three B’s are going to vote to approve the closing costs, around 9,000 thousand dollars, for the 2.6 million in property. The B’s, all white, want the hwy 13 property while the community has voiced it’s desire for the twin beech property close to the black community, but that is not where the honey is.<wp:post_name><![CDATA[honey-bees]]>
</wp:post_name>
<wp:post_name><![CDATA[corridor-of-chaos]]>
</wp:post_name>
<wp:meta_value><![CDATA[PODCAST LIVE TODAY &#x2d; Old Battles Place will have 94 units and now THE “CORRIDOR OF CHAOS”. 232 Apartments, 77 single family houses and 16 commercial units.]]></wp:meta_value>
<wp:meta_value><![CDATA[https://cdn.rippreport.com/wp-content/uploads/2019/10/cropped-catalyst-logo-fb.png]]></wp:meta_value>

<wp:post_name><![CDATA[backstory-podcast-6]]>
</wp:post_name>
<wp:post_name><![CDATA[fairhope-sold-to-the-highest-bidder]]>
</wp:post_name>	
<wp:post_name><![CDATA[going-down]]>
</wp:post_name>
<wp:meta_value><![CDATA[https://cdn.rippreport.com/wp-content/uploads/2019/10/cropped-fairhope-water.jpg]]></wp:meta_value>

<wp:post_name><![CDATA[backstory-podcast-7]]>
</wp:post_name>That is why I don’t watch local tv news.    			
<wp:post_name><![CDATA[tonight]]>
</wp:post_name>
<wp:meta_value><![CDATA[https://cdn.rippreport.com/wp-content/uploads/2019/10/night-fb.jpg]]></wp:meta_value>
<wp:meta_value><![CDATA[TONIGHT &#x2d; THE RIPP REPORT &#x2d; BACKSTORY PODCAST]]></wp:meta_value>
<wp:meta_value><![CDATA[The public is invited to a free Special Screening of “Stories in Rhyme &#x2d; The Songwriters of the Flora&#x2d;Bama Lounge” at 6 p.m. at the Gulf State Park Conservation Hall. Doors open at 5:45 p.m.]]></wp:meta_value>
		What am I missing here?    I look forward to your Wonderful Wednesday posts and this week I get this?
Baldwin County should be renamed “Quid Quo Pro County”<wp:post_name><![CDATA[watering-hole]]>
</wp:post_name>
<wp:meta_value><![CDATA[How does a bar owner, continuously break the law and walk? If you are Ronan McSharry it appears not to be a problem.]]></wp:meta_value>
<wp:meta_value><![CDATA[https://cdn.rippreport.com/wp-content/uploads/2019/10/mcsharry-fb.jpg]]></wp:meta_value>
<wp:meta_value><![CDATA[WATERING HOLE &#x2d; THE RIPP REPORT]]></wp:meta_value>
<wp:meta_value><![CDATA[How does a bar owner, continuously break the law and walk? If you are Ronan McSharry it appears not to be a problem.]]></wp:meta_value>

You will hear much more about this good ole boy deal because people are already coming forward with details and information never made public. This should be the nail in the coffin for the city council in 2020.This is in your face corruption with ?CATALYST fingerprints all over it.Be aware folks the Fairhope City Council is 100% ?CATALYST. For those of you who do not know who ?CATALYST is, just understand that they do not represent the Citizens of Fairhope or Baldwin County.<wp:post_name><![CDATA[nail-in-the-coffin]]>
</wp:post_name>
<wp:meta_value><![CDATA[??? ???? ? ?????? ⚖️ ʙᴀʟᴅᴡɪɴ ᴄᴏᴜɴᴛʏ ʟᴇɢᴀʟ ᴇᴀɢʟᴇ ⚖️]]></wp:meta_value>
<wp:meta_value><![CDATA[⚰️ ?【﻿???? ?? ??? ??????】⚰️ ?]]></wp:meta_value>
<wp:meta_value><![CDATA[https://cdn.rippreport.com/wp-content/uploads/2019/10/nail-in-the-coffin.png]]></wp:meta_value>

<wp:post_name><![CDATA[saturday-apology]]>
</wp:post_name>
<wp:meta_value><![CDATA[SATURDAY APOLOGY &#x2d; THE RIPP REPORT &#x2d; BACKSTORY PODCAST]]></wp:meta_value>
<wp:meta_value><![CDATA[https://cdn.rippreport.com/wp-content/uploads/2019/11/cropped-podcast-fb.jpg]]></wp:meta_value>
<wp:meta_value><![CDATA[6108]]></wp:meta_value>

This is exactly why Alabama and Baldwin County are so corrupt. You are going to be told by Council and the good Judge “<strong>That nothing is wrong with the council approving a development for the Judge they appointed.</strong>"I hope the Junior Council of Fairhope is paying attention to their “leaders”. The Jr. Council should run a candidate for City Council 2020 because the present “senior” council is selling out Fairhope.<wp:post_name><![CDATA[catalyst-colors]]>
</wp:post_name>
<wp:meta_value><![CDATA[6147]]></wp:meta_value>
<wp:meta_value><![CDATA[? CATALYST COLORS ?]]></wp:meta_value>
<wp:meta_value><![CDATA[... the 3 B’s, ? Burrell, ? Brown and ? Boone, approved and purchased, 2.65 million in land for recreation, that did NOT have the approval of National Park Service.]]></wp:meta_value>
<wp:meta_value><![CDATA[https://cdn.rippreport.com/wp-content/uploads/2019/11/cropped-catalyst-fb.jpg]]></wp:meta_value>
<wp:meta_value><![CDATA[6149]]></wp:meta_value>

<wp:post_name><![CDATA[conflict-on-interest]]>
</wp:post_name>
<wp:meta_value><![CDATA[? ???????? ?? ???????? ??‍⚖️ ??? ???? ? ?????? &#x2d; ????????? ???????]]></wp:meta_value>
<wp:meta_value><![CDATA[How can a city council approve the largest development in Fairhope when the Municipal Judge is the developer...]]></wp:meta_value>

Backstory Podcast<wp:post_name><![CDATA[read-and-listen]]>
</wp:post_name>
<wp:meta_value><![CDATA[6174]]></wp:meta_value>
<wp:meta_value><![CDATA[READ AND LISTEN]]></wp:meta_value>
<wp:meta_value><![CDATA[No ethics, No transparency, No accountability, No good]]></wp:meta_value>
<wp:meta_value><![CDATA[https://cdn.rippreport.com/wp-content/uploads/2019/11/cropped-readandlisten.jpg]]></wp:meta_value>
<wp:meta_value><![CDATA[6177]]></wp:meta_value>
<wp:meta_value><![CDATA[https://rippreport.com/2019/11/20/read-and-listen/]]></wp:meta_value>

<wp:post_name><![CDATA[backstory-podcast-12]]>
</wp:post_name>
<wp:meta_value><![CDATA[? BACKSTORY PODCAST 12 ? ?]]></wp:meta_value>
<wp:meta_value><![CDATA[Poarch Creek Indians make a $1 Billion Dollar offer to the State of Alabama: all they want is a monopoly in return...]]></wp:meta_value>
<wp:meta_value><![CDATA[https://cdn.rippreport.com/wp-content/uploads/2019/11/klump2.jpeg]]></wp:meta_value>
<wp:meta_value><![CDATA[6179]]></wp:meta_value>
	I am remembering all this when I vote next year
This is political and the political machine is still driving the same plan to obstruct development of the triangle. Be it a park or conservation easement or what ever else they dream up.One thing I know for sure this will end in a class action lawsuit or the entire council will be voted out of office, or both.<wp:post_name><![CDATA[triangle-roaches]]>
</wp:post_name>			
<wp:post_name><![CDATA[combat]]>
</wp:post_name>	
Just read in the Lagniappe of the dirty dealings of the usual suspects<wp:post_name><![CDATA[christmas]]>
</wp:post_name>
<wp:meta_value><![CDATA[6308]]></wp:meta_value>

WATCH UNTIL MINUTE 2:07–9:03<wp:post_name><![CDATA[criminal-enterprise]]>
</wp:post_name>
<wp:meta_value><![CDATA[6313]]></wp:meta_value>

<wp:post_name><![CDATA[backstory-podcast-15-the-banquette]]>
</wp:post_name>
<wp:post_name><![CDATA[rotten]]>
</wp:post_name>
<wp:meta_value><![CDATA[6322]]></wp:meta_value>

<wp:post_name><![CDATA[backstory-podcast-16-the-jack-wilson-complex]]>
</wp:post_name>
<wp:post_name><![CDATA[malfunction-junction]]>
</wp:post_name>
<wp:post_name><![CDATA[off-the-rails]]>
</wp:post_name>
<wp:meta_value><![CDATA[6341]]></wp:meta_value>
<wp:meta_value><![CDATA[OFF THE RAILS - BACKSTORY LIVE TODAY]]></wp:meta_value>
<wp:meta_value><![CDATA[Consider Fairhope just had another sewer spill...]]></wp:meta_value>
<wp:meta_value><![CDATA[https://cdn.rippreport.com/wp-content/uploads/2020/01/cropped-off-rails-fb-1.jpg]]></wp:meta_value>
<wp:meta_value><![CDATA[6343]]></wp:meta_value>

New Year Prediction: The City Council, Catalyst, and the status quo are now going to obstruct the use of the Triangle.Get ready folks this is going to be so much BS you will need boots. Marble Mouth will be at his best.They want to take municipal property, that taxpayers paid 8.75 million for, plus 3 million in attorney fees, and give control of the land to a third party.Wake up Fairhope, Marble Mouth, the council and the great Negotiator, are costing taxpayers millions while ignoring infrastructure, sewers, and capital projects.They have NO PLAN and they ALL need to be kicked out of office.<wp:post_name><![CDATA[marble-mouth]]>
</wp:post_name>
<wp:meta_value><![CDATA[6359]]></wp:meta_value>
<wp:meta_value><![CDATA[https://cdn.rippreport.com/wp-content/uploads/2020/01/cropped-Jay-Robinson-fb.jpeg]]></wp:meta_value>
<wp:meta_value><![CDATA[6361]]></wp:meta_value>
	Turd floaters at the kpier.
<script async defer crossorigin="anonymous" src="https://connect.facebook.net/en_US/sdk.js#xfbml=1&version=v5.0&appId=826483077484358&autoLogAppEvents=1"></script><wp:post_name><![CDATA[backstory-podcast-2]]>
</wp:post_name>
You have four other choices for Congressmen, that are NOT CATALYST. Please tell your friends and family, the last thing we need is for CATALYST to be our congressional representative.<wp:post_name><![CDATA[congressional-catalyst]]>
</wp:post_name>
<wp:meta_value><![CDATA[6396]]></wp:meta_value>

<wp:post_name><![CDATA[bar-stool-continued]]>
</wp:post_name>
<wp:meta_value><![CDATA[https://cdn.rippreport.com/wp-content/uploads/2020/01/cropped-barstool.jpg]]></wp:meta_value>
<wp:meta_value><![CDATA[6406]]></wp:meta_value>

<wp:post_name><![CDATA[catalyst-central]]>
</wp:post_name>
<wp:meta_value><![CDATA[3795]]></wp:meta_value>

<wp:post_name><![CDATA[fairhope-state-of-the-city]]>
</wp:post_name>
<wp:meta_value><![CDATA[6419]]></wp:meta_value>
<wp:meta_value><![CDATA[for over 5 million, which needs roof repairs. The main city hall needs a new roof and recreation upgrades within the city are needed.]]></wp:meta_value>
	What makes Catalyst at its core, whatever it is called?  Is it the politicians that utilize it?  Is it the developers that fund it?  We need to be able to identify this group because Ripp has exposed what it does which is corrupt government.
<wp:post_name><![CDATA[survey]]>
</wp:post_name>
<wp:meta_value><![CDATA[6434]]></wp:meta_value>
<wp:meta_value><![CDATA[Last night’s, State of the City of Fairhope, was a success and the employees represented the city proudly.]]></wp:meta_value>
<wp:meta_value><![CDATA[https://cdn.rippreport.com/wp-content/uploads/2020/02/cropped-fb-waterfront.jpg]]></wp:meta_value>
<wp:meta_value><![CDATA[6437]]></wp:meta_value>
	To the rest of the council: From Boone to the banker baby to marble mouth to Brown hometown.   We are coming to vote you out 
<wp:post_name><![CDATA[catalyst-kiss]]>
</wp:post_name>Clean sweep 2020.
<wp:post_name><![CDATA[danger-zone]]>
</wp:post_name>
<wp:meta_value><![CDATA[6454]]></wp:meta_value>

https://mynbc15.com/news/local/medical-marijuana-bill-heads-to-first-vote-in-alabama-legislature?fbclid=IwAR2iwv_sHDYjvn2RY2p8sBB6zkboDlXcnO6e429ViQToj3wqJuaNYGuCrco</a><wp:post_name><![CDATA[medical-marijuana-bill-heads-to-first-vote-in-alabama-legislature]]>
</wp:post_name>
<wp:meta_value><![CDATA[6458]]></wp:meta_value>
<wp:meta_value><![CDATA[6456]]></wp:meta_value>
<wp:meta_value><![CDATA[https://cdn.rippreport.com/wp-content/uploads/2020/02/cropped-Cannabis_leaf.jpg]]></wp:meta_value>
<wp:meta_value><![CDATA[6463]]></wp:meta_value>

<wp:post_name><![CDATA[election-ad]]>
</wp:post_name>
<wp:post_name><![CDATA[backwoods-media-ad]]>
</wp:post_name>
<wp:meta_value><![CDATA[6510]]></wp:meta_value>
<wp:meta_value><![CDATA[https://cdn.rippreport.com/wp-content/uploads/2020/02/cropped-backwoods-ad-1.jpg]]></wp:meta_value>
<wp:meta_value><![CDATA[6515]]></wp:meta_value>
<wp:meta_value><![CDATA[Backwoods Media LLC Ad]]></wp:meta_value>

<wp:post_name><![CDATA[catalyst-virus]]>
</wp:post_name>
<wp:meta_value><![CDATA[6520]]></wp:meta_value>
<wp:meta_value><![CDATA[CATALYST VIRUS - THE RIPP REPORT]]></wp:meta_value>
<wp:meta_value><![CDATA[To prevent the virus do not vote for any CATALYST candidates March 3, TOMORROW]]></wp:meta_value>
	How can we know if a candidate is Catalyst or not?	Are you really  going to use that moolah you won against Jack and his four butties on the council? 	
<wp:post_name><![CDATA[runoff]]>
</wp:post_name>
<wp:meta_value><![CDATA[6524]]></wp:meta_value>

As a Jerry Carl supporter, this post reflects my personal opinion, and not the opinion of this group.You might think I'm crazy for putting Bill Hightower's social media statement out there for everyone to see. But I really want people to read this thing, and when I say read it, I want you to read between the lines. This statement personifies exactly what I've been talking about when it comes to Bill Hightower.I guess he thinks we're not smart enough to figure out that this is a political campaign. You don't win political campaigns by putting out positive ads about your opponent.He wants to put his personal friendship with Jerry Carl on his shirt sleeve. After reading the second paragraph of his statement, he has no problem throwing his so-called friend under the bus with personal non-political dirty laundry.Lets assume Bill Hightower's accusation about Jerry is correct about him borrowing like $200,000 to pay for his political campaign, I say, God love him. What in the Hell is wrong with that?Bill Hightower is telling us that Jerry Carl went to the bank for $200,000 for his own campaign instead of following Bill Hightowers example oof prostituting himself out to every out of state special interest group that's willing to hand him cash.Compared to Bill hightower's warchest of special interest money, Jerry has to do what he has to do in order to compete with Daddy Warbucks. He has to level the playing field if he wants any chance of winning.Remember, every Hightower campaign ad you are going to see during this run off has already been bought and paid for by out-of-state special interest money. And trust me it adds up to more than what Jerry Carl supposedly borrowed from the bank.In the end, the debt has to be paid back. Jerry may have to pay back a bank, but who do you think Hightower is going to owe?Like I said, read his statement very carefuilly, read between the lines. If anything, Hightowers own words seem to reflect who is truely the desperate man.FROM BILL REGARDING JERRY CARL'S NEW FALSE, NEGATIVE ATTACK AD:I am disappointed in Jerry’s decision to start the run-off campaign with these negative attack ads. My wife Susan and I always considered him a friend. Heck, he supported my prior campaigns. He knows me, he knows that I was rated one of the most conservative legislators in Montgomery, and he konws these attacks are simply untrue.Campaigns are tough on candidates and they are tough on their families. We understand the stress Jerry must be feeling. I think it is telling that his campaign is over a half-million dollars in debt, over $200,000 of which is owed to a local bank. That would make anyone act out of desperation. But we thought Jerry was better than resorting to distortions and negative TV ads to achieve his personal political aspirations. I guess campaigns reveal the true heart of a candidate.<wp:post_name><![CDATA[public-servant]]>
</wp:post_name>
<wp:meta_value><![CDATA[6533]]></wp:meta_value>

<wp:post_name><![CDATA[fairhope-council-asleep-at-the-wheel]]>
</wp:post_name>
<wp:meta_value><![CDATA[6540]]></wp:meta_value>
<wp:meta_value><![CDATA[...CATALYST council is asleep at the wheel. Coronavirus and the Arts and Craft Festival, HB 203, and Fly Creek Apartments.]]></wp:meta_value>
	I blame Burrell.
<wp:post_name><![CDATA[catalyst-2]]>
</wp:post_name>
<wp:meta_value><![CDATA[3795]]></wp:meta_value>

<wp:post_name><![CDATA[virus-vs-catalyst]]>
</wp:post_name>
<wp:meta_value><![CDATA[6552]]></wp:meta_value>
	You want examples?
<wp:post_name><![CDATA[economic-virus]]>
</wp:post_name>
<wp:meta_value><![CDATA[6559]]></wp:meta_value>

<wp:post_name><![CDATA[lost-opportunity]]>
</wp:post_name>
<wp:meta_value><![CDATA[6563]]></wp:meta_value>

In Alabama the virus and politics are a lot alike. Either you educate yourself or you become an APRIL FOOL.<wp:post_name><![CDATA[april-fool]]>
</wp:post_name>
<wp:meta_value><![CDATA[6568]]></wp:meta_value>
<wp:meta_value><![CDATA[In Alabama some citizens are participating a 100%, at the potential risk of others.]]></wp:meta_value>
	Do you REALLY think people are going to imprison themselves for a whole month?
<wp:post_name><![CDATA[shelter-in-place]]>
</wp:post_name>
<wp:meta_value><![CDATA[6583]]></wp:meta_value>
<wp:meta_value><![CDATA[Since the report below was posted, in less than 12 hours, the number of cases has risen by 136 cases and deaths are at 36.]]></wp:meta_value>
<wp:meta_value><![CDATA[https://cdn.rippreport.com/wp-content/uploads/2020/04/cropped-fb-shelter.jpg]]></wp:meta_value>
<wp:meta_value><![CDATA[6590]]></wp:meta_value>
<wp:meta_value><![CDATA[Since the report below was posted, in less than 12 hours, the number of cases has risen by 136 cases and deaths are at 36.]]></wp:meta_value>

<wp:post_name><![CDATA[the-fairhope-jester]]>
</wp:post_name>
<wp:meta_value><![CDATA[6594]]></wp:meta_value>
<wp:meta_value><![CDATA[https://cdn.rippreport.com/wp-content/uploads/2020/04/cropped-robertbrownfb.jpg]]></wp:meta_value>
<wp:meta_value><![CDATA[6596]]></wp:meta_value>

<wp:post_name><![CDATA[pissed-on-or-pissed-off]]>
</wp:post_name>
<wp:meta_value><![CDATA[6604]]></wp:meta_value>
	When the people go back to work on May 1, and they will, the economic damage will be devastating and history will see how silly we were.   We are a generation of weaklings
CATALYST wants Sherry Sullivan as their next candidate for Mayor of Fairhope. This is their way of injecting her name, otherwise most would not even know who she is. A former city employee who had numerous jobs, none for long. She briefly was in charge of the recreation center, she failed miserable.New Orleans and Mobile are having a difficult time with COVID-19 and there is little argument that Mardi Gras was the culprit.What do you think would have happened if Burrell, Brown and Sullivan had gotten their wish and had the “take a chance Arts and Craft Show”? Fairhope Mayor Wilson and a couple of council members almost certainly prevented the opportunity of COVID-19 being exposed to as many as 200,000 attendees.16. Resolution – That the City of Fairhope has voted to purchase one (1) E-ONE Custom Rescue Pumper Fire Truck for Fire Station #1 and the vehicle is available for direct procurement through the Houston-Galveston Area Council Contract FS12-19 which has been nationally bid; and therefore, does not have to be let out for bid. The total cost is $517,157.000. This is a joint purchase between the City of Fairhope and the Fairhope Volunteer Fire Department with a 60/40 split. The City is paying up to $331,000.00 from Impact Fees and the Fairhope Volunteer Fire Department is paying up to $200,000.00.Burrell stated that the Volunteer Fire Department was “Gracious” in donating 200 thousand dollars towards the purchase of the Custom Fire Truck. Burrell did not mention that only a few months ago the fire chief told the Mayor in council chambers that he would not provide the city with any financial s. He was rude and made a speech that the fire department did not have to tell the Mayor anything, they were independent, but they take city money!The city pays 331,000.00 and Burrell says the fire department is “GRACIOUS” for contributing 200,000.00. Fairhope needs a full time fire department, that are employees of the city and answer to the city.COVID-19 should be taken seriously and it is not the time or place to be talking about political rallies disguised as a party.<wp:post_name><![CDATA[catalyst-party]]>
</wp:post_name>
The assault charge, Stankoski dropped was based on the fact that the municipal attorney, Marcus McDowell, failed to amend the charge of assault, to include: ”did cause bodily harm”, on the Fairhope charging document. It seems a year went by and McDowell failed to amend the original complaint. If you believe this I have some stock in a gold mine in Belize that you may be interested in investing in.Here is the Backstory. McDowell, unsuccessfully represented Burrell when Burrell as council president denied me the ability to speak at a city council meeting. Burrell is best buddies with McSherry. So we are to believe that McDowell forgot for over a year, as city prosecutor, to amend the assault charge? Now, all those delays seem to be part of a larger plan. McDowell should be fired, but wait the council would have to do that, and he is their lawyer???McSherry has not spent a day in jail and has been to Fairhope municipal court multiple times. Municipal Judge Snedeker accepted McSherry’s guilty plea and sentenced him to 180 days in jail and credited him with two months he :allegedly” spent in re-hab.The intoxication charge is pending and Diniardi has filed a civil charge against McSherry. Judge Stankoski is presiding over the civil case as well. What’s the next trick?Four years ago we elected a new Mayor and council. The Mayor wanted a fresh start and a new city attorney as well as a municipal judge. The CATALYST council wanted the old “established” attorney and judge. Since that time both Judge and Attorney have been embroiled in several highly political issues, where their loyalties were clearly in favor of the CATALYST council, not the citizens of Fairhope.<wp:post_name><![CDATA[judicial-trick]]>
</wp:post_name>
<wp:meta_value><![CDATA[6619]]></wp:meta_value>
<wp:meta_value><![CDATA[682]]></wp:meta_value>
	He is fearless.    Ripp, aren’t you afraid that somebody in the Catalyst group will want to shut you up?
<wp:post_name><![CDATA[american-citizen]]>
</wp:post_name>
<wp:meta_value><![CDATA[6629]]></wp:meta_value>
<wp:meta_value><![CDATA[...CATALYST, corruption and judicial failure, is all exposed in one incident, the McSherry assault case.]]></wp:meta_value>

<wp:post_name><![CDATA[where-is-justice]]>
</wp:post_name>
<wp:meta_value><![CDATA[6635]]></wp:meta_value>

<wp:post_name><![CDATA[money-on-the-table]]>
</wp:post_name>
<wp:meta_value><![CDATA[6643]]></wp:meta_value>
<wp:meta_value><![CDATA[...projects that have been previously endorsed by the council, are delayed or canceled by the council.]]></wp:meta_value>
		Whoa. Fraud? They claimed it was for recreation and then switched?Has this been scrutinized through foia? Who owned the land? Who got the 2.6 mill?
<wp:post_name><![CDATA[backstory-podcast-35-contrarians]]>
</wp:post_name>
CATALYST will do anything possible to regain Fairhope as their power base, including fixing elections, if the can.<wp:post_name><![CDATA[catalyst-candidates-%e2%81%a0-excess-baggage]]>
</wp:post_name>
<wp:meta_value><![CDATA[6655]]></wp:meta_value>

<wp:post_name><![CDATA[catalyst-players]]>
</wp:post_name>
Paula DiNardi is a victim of physical assault and the city attorney, has exhibited total incompetence in his handling of the case. Now he is suggesting that the intoxication charge and the assault charge carry the “identical punishments”.So the city attorney wants you to believe even though he dropped the ball a thousand times on the assault charge, and it may disappear, he will pursue the “other” charge, intoxication.What total bullshit.So what happens with the $10,000 dollars in medical bills Paula sustained?She also lost her job has suffered with the stress of something she had nothing to do with. She went to a restaurant/bar to relax and a bully assaults her knocking her off a bar stool.This could be any woman and the Fairhope City Council turns a blind eye.Ronan McSharry is a public nuisance, a repeat offender of the law, a bully of women and a public drunk. He is a danger to the general public and if he is not stopped he will continue to violate the law.<wp:post_name><![CDATA[catalyst-justice]]>
</wp:post_name>
<wp:meta_value><![CDATA[6676]]></wp:meta_value>
<wp:meta_value><![CDATA[How many people remember Sen Tripp Pittman and his theft of BP money to the tune of $750,000 dollars?]]></wp:meta_value>

<wp:post_name><![CDATA[catalyst-shit-creek]]>
</wp:post_name>
<wp:meta_value><![CDATA[6680]]></wp:meta_value>
<wp:meta_value><![CDATA[...interesting that all the complaints about Fly Creek and Publix were ignored by ADEM, Alabama Department of Environmental Management...]]></wp:meta_value>

CATALYST is bad enough but Burrell represents the worst of CATALYST.Burrell is number one on the list to vote out, Aug. 25th.Qualification for Fairhope municipal elections is July 7th to July 21.<wp:post_name><![CDATA[catalyst-liar]]>
</wp:post_name>
<wp:meta_value><![CDATA[6683]]></wp:meta_value>
<wp:meta_value><![CDATA[Not only is Council Burrell a bald faced liar, he thinks a hard hat works better than a face mask.]]></wp:meta_value>

<wp:post_name><![CDATA[dark-wednesday]]>
</wp:post_name>
<wp:meta_value><![CDATA[6692]]></wp:meta_value>

The McSharry case is corruption staring you in the face. Ask yourself what if this was your daughter, sister, mother or friend that was assaulted? The City Attorney, failed, numerous times, in error or purpose, to defend the victim. He should be fired. The city will be lucky if they are not sued for the way this case has been handled.After the bully council is lectured about their treatment of women, Councilman Boone, aka llc. Boone, starts yelling at the Mayor and demanding Councilman Burrell immediately adjourn the meeting, which he did. Burrell cut off the Mayor’s comments after he had just pledged to her “she would be given the opportunity to speak.”I hope every woman in Baldwin County sees this video. This is CATALYST and what they stand for, THEMSELVES. Men that treat women like this are not men, but cowards.<wp:post_name><![CDATA[catalyst-train-wreck]]>
</wp:post_name>
<wp:meta_value><![CDATA[6700]]></wp:meta_value>

<wp:post_name><![CDATA[paradise-lost-ii]]>
</wp:post_name>
<wp:meta_value><![CDATA[6705]]></wp:meta_value>

<wp:post_name><![CDATA[warner-to-sign-copies-of-new-tailgaters-guide-to-sec-football-at-page-palette-june-6th]]>
</wp:post_name>
<wp:meta_value><![CDATA[6703]]></wp:meta_value>

<wp:post_name><![CDATA[strawman-spiderweb]]>
</wp:post_name>
<wp:meta_value><![CDATA[6725]]></wp:meta_value>
<wp:meta_value><![CDATA[682]]></wp:meta_value>

<wp:post_name><![CDATA[a-decade-of-corruption]]>
</wp:post_name>
<wp:meta_value><![CDATA[6727]]></wp:meta_value>
<wp:meta_value><![CDATA[Baldwin County is a cesspool of political and judicial corruption. In the last 10 years...]]></wp:meta_value>

<wp:post_name><![CDATA[faux-candidates]]>
</wp:post_name>
<wp:meta_value><![CDATA[6732]]></wp:meta_value>
<wp:meta_value><![CDATA[It is election time and CATALYST is at work stroking FAUX candidates that are willing to fall on the sword for CATALYST.]]></wp:meta_value>

<wp:post_name><![CDATA[bradley-byrne-endorses-jerry-carl-in-gop-runoff-for-his-district-1-seat]]>
</wp:post_name>
<wp:post_name><![CDATA[stealing-our-democracy]]>
</wp:post_name>
<wp:meta_value><![CDATA[6742]]></wp:meta_value>
<wp:meta_value><![CDATA[When elections are “fixed” you can be assured, politicians, any party, are STEALING OUR DEMOCRACY.]]></wp:meta_value>

<wp:post_name><![CDATA[where-hell-were-you]]>
</wp:post_name>
<wp:meta_value><![CDATA[6747]]></wp:meta_value>
<wp:meta_value><![CDATA[Fairhope is closing in on another municipal election so get ready for CATALYST and the ill informed to try and convince voters that they know best.]]></wp:meta_value>

<wp:post_name><![CDATA[invitation]]>
</wp:post_name>
<wp:meta_value><![CDATA[6752]]></wp:meta_value>
<wp:meta_value><![CDATA[Fairhope Mayor Wilson is inviting the citizens of Fairhope, again, to participate in...]]></wp:meta_value>

<wp:post_name><![CDATA[fairhope-waterfront]]>
</wp:post_name>
<wp:meta_value><![CDATA[6434]]></wp:meta_value>
<wp:meta_value><![CDATA[The Fairhope Waterfront project started off with, City Council approval, of $500,000.00 for engineering and conceptual plans based on community input.]]></wp:meta_value>

<wp:post_name><![CDATA[catalyst-stacking-the-deck]]>
</wp:post_name>
<wp:post_name><![CDATA[backstory-podcast-43-mee-maw-and-the-extenders]]>
</wp:post_name>
<wp:post_name><![CDATA[fourth-of-july-2]]>
</wp:post_name>
<wp:meta_value><![CDATA[6778]]></wp:meta_value>

<wp:post_name><![CDATA[howling-rains]]>
</wp:post_name>
<wp:meta_value><![CDATA[6783]]></wp:meta_value>
<wp:meta_value><![CDATA[Baldwin County has seen its share of political commentary from Baldwin Insider, The Jester and the Infamous “Chuckie Cheeze” who quite appropriately now works...]]></wp:meta_value>

for Congress</p><wp:post_name><![CDATA[attention-baldwin-county]]>
</wp:post_name>
<wp:meta_value><![CDATA[6760]]></wp:meta_value>
<wp:meta_value><![CDATA[Vote Jerry Carl July 14th for Congress "Lowtower" is ? CATALYST ?]]></wp:meta_value>

To the editor:This could be long — I hope it’s not inflammatory — it’s not meant to be. This is to all of the non-mask wearing and partying people out there.I am mad. I am worried. And I am scared. And you, who refuse to wear a mask, and congregate with your friends, are the reason!!! You are endangering my family. And my friends. And ME!When I look at you and see intelligent people who normally use common sense, and are active in philanthropy, and usually show such empathy for others, I am shocked. I KNOW you aren’t the selfish people you seem to have become. Yes, selfish. Because by behaving the way you are, you are basically saying that you are only interested in what is good for YOU at this time, and that the health and welfare of everyone else with whom you come in contact really isn’t your concern. The numbers are SPIKING. And the demographic that is testing positive now is YOU!But you are also transmitting it to your families. You have parents who are at high risk. You have children at home who, often when they get COVID-19, don’t display the same symptoms, and get much sicker.Trust me — we ALL want to get out and have fun with our friends. We ALL are sick of cooking every single night. We ALL want to see our children and grandchildren. But we can’t because YOU ARE, and you are spreading this virus.Those of us in the older generation have worked and saved and done without when you were all growing up so that you could have the wonderful memories of childhood that you have! And so that you could enjoy the wonderful lives you all have today. We also hoped that, upon retirement, we could do the things we gave up to get to this point in our lives. And you are STEALING that from us! We are now spending our Golden Years in the four walls of our homes, unable to go out socially, unable to play with our grandchildren, unable to take those fabulous vacations we had planned for.I beg you — PLEASE — stop the partying. Stop the congregating. Start wearing masks in public! Don’t let the world blame you for spreading this insidious disease!Thank you for reading this!Jani Handwerger<wp:post_name><![CDATA[wear-a-mask]]>
</wp:post_name>
The three B’s are all running for re-election on the council. Boone, Brown and Burrell have used their office for personal gain and Burrell has a Police Report he never mentioned in the last election.https://rippreport.com/2018/05/23/police-report/They want the full family insurance package that they voted in, and all have used, estimated at $17,500. and all the deals they can get on the side. These three sidewinders pulled of the worst deal in history. They and I mean they, the 3 of them, without public participation and breaking a promise to the black community, purchased farmland for recreation property. The land is farmland and they have no money for development so they promptly leased the land back to a farmer for $9000 dollars a year. Yes you read that correctly, 9 Thousand. They took a city surplus of 1.7 million and drove it to a 1.2 million dollar deficient, overnight. Expect to hear HOWLING telling us that they are all Christians.Next week July 21st, is the last day of qualification, let’s hope a challenger steps up for each Council seat. The current council desperately needs replacing, they have been the worst council in 25 years.Attend the meetings on the Waterfront, do not listen to the HOWLING RAIN. GET THE FACTShttps://rippreport.com/2020/06/26/fairhope-waterfront/<wp:post_name><![CDATA[freaky-fairhope]]>
</wp:post_name>
<wp:meta_value><![CDATA[6792]]></wp:meta_value>
<wp:meta_value><![CDATA[After living in Fairhope for 25 years and spending 16 years of close observation of local politics, nothing surprises me.]]></wp:meta_value>

<wp:post_name><![CDATA[vote-jerry-carl-today]]>
</wp:post_name>
<wp:post_name><![CDATA[sting]]>
</wp:post_name>
<wp:post_name><![CDATA[history-repeating-itself]]>
</wp:post_name>wp:meta_value><![CDATA[6801]]></wp:meta_value>
<wp:meta_value><![CDATA[I am writing in response to Mr. Howell Raines’ op&#x2d;ed and his follow up Letter to the Editor, referencing the Fairhope waterfront.]]></wp:meta_value>
<wp:meta_value><![CDATA[6800]]></wp:meta_value>

<wp:post_name><![CDATA[catalyst-ass-whoopin]]>
</wp:post_name>
<wp:meta_value><![CDATA[6807]]></wp:meta_value>
<wp:meta_value><![CDATA[Fairhope’s CATALYST group is licking their wounds after the election of Jerry Carl.]]></wp:meta_value>

Is it that, if approved, this might make her look as though she was busy working and finding resources to better the City?I think the grant from the oil spill was supposed to be used to better the City; that money was allocated to our City and the money from that grant was awarded in a no bid contract was paid to a private contractor who was friends with the last Mayor. They didn’t even put on a robber mask go rob the City. They thought they were entitled to that money. A large portion of that could have been used for needed infrastructure. That sort of thing is unethical and unfair to taxpayers. And the complacency in accepting stealing? Why would we think anything about this should be acceptable? We live in a world of transparency now, and those sort of transactions come to light. Nothing, and I mean nothing about that was for the good of the citizens of Fairhope. Well, maybe two.You are a good person, I knew your Mama. She used to tell me about Robert all the time. I am from the same cloth. I am honest and hardworking as well.I think we all have a vested interest in Fairhope and that we do not allow politics of the past to continue to dictate the future of Fairhope.Thank you for allowing me to voice my opinion.<wp:post_name><![CDATA[truth]]>
</wp:post_name>
<wp:meta_value><![CDATA[6815]]></wp:meta_value>
<wp:meta_value><![CDATA[683]]></wp:meta_value>
<wp:meta_value><![CDATA[In response to Councilman Brown about his position on the Waterfront... The public bay front has evolved and seen many changes over the course of my lifetime]]></wp:meta_value>

End Wasteful Spending & Restore Fiscal HealthFour years ago, the city was running an annual $6 Million deficit, making payments on millions of dollars of debt, and requiring most of the profits from our Utility department to subsidize its budget.Today, the City is fiscally self-reliant, paid off long-term debt, increased combined City/Utility cash funds by almost 60% leaving our gas, electric, water and wastewater utilities the ability to finally afford its long-ignored maintenance and upgrade needs.In addition, my administration obtained $18M in RESTORE funds, most of which will be invested in sewer system upgrades and a sewer overflow prevention plan along the Eastern Shore - money citizens will save in sewer rate increases.This is what fiscal responsibility looks like and will continue under my leadership as a fiscal conservative with ~30 years experience in Finance & Business Management.This is a promise - like the ones I made in 2016 for which I delivered. Let’s stay the course moving forward together.Vote KarinForFairhope.org August 2th<wp:post_name><![CDATA[catalyst-last-stand]]>
</wp:post_name>
I hope that everyone understands what is really at stake here!Sherry says “ she knows how city government should be work, about how building relationships is important in order to get things done “ …. WELL FOLKS, YES SHE DOES!!!She was a huge part of the Kant regime that was full of corruption, did work and favors for wealthy people and maintained these poisonous relationships that were good for the administration but not good for the city. The prior administration had a cottage industry going; among them they billed legal hours and hours and hours on issues that could have been sewn up in one hour. They had a money making machine going, and a license to steal. By the way, honk when you drive by Hand Arendale’s law office on the corner of Section and Magnolia? Oh! Is it not there anymore? Wonder if she will put those folks back into play?She was a player in not investing in our infrastructure and keeping it up to standards, giving contracts to friends.SHE was part of the problem! SHE WAS AND IS ON THAT TEAM!After Wilson was elected, Sherry kept in her position because of Wilson’s olive branch to the old Kant regime – she intended on keeping every department head in place. Some of these folks couldn’t seem to accept that Karin was their boss. They seemed to think it was more important to be disruptive and sneaky and try and put their feet in the sand to make Wilson look bad. Is that how you build relationships? By being passive aggressive and then playing the victim???? That is EXACTLY how she played it.She drug poor Joseph, the vulnerable and kind Chief of Police,up in front of the City Council, with her other fired department heads, she orchestrated the town leaders to speak on Joseph’s behalf, Jack a** B tore up his letter of resignation and the whole town applauded. It was grandstanding, USING Joseph as a means to embarrass and humiliate Mayor Wilson. But, there were so many of us who could see through this drama. Joseph himself, was unaware that he told the tale when he said he called Mayor Kant to tell him he was resigning. Well, Kant was not your boss any longer. That seems to have been a theme. The couldn’t quit Kant.They couldn’t be positive and accept change and work with their new boss. They would rather have seen Wilson fail so they cut off their noses to spit their faces. And drama is what they LOVE!!!!They don’t care about Fairhope as much as they care about themselves and what they can do for the good ol’ boys!Wilson thought that they could all be adults and work together. She had EVERY RIGHT, to replace Sherry and the others on day one. Yet Sherry persists in defining herself as the “fired” candidate.You never entered the Mayor Kant’s office without Sherry being there and two steps behind to sniff out everyone’s business. “ Is there anything I can do to help?” was ALWAYS her spew.Do we really want to go back to that select group of people who have been here for generations and their machine is for themselves and not the citizens of Fairhope as a whole. Do we really want the current council to continue to be openly rude and condescending and disrespectful to the person we selected as our Mayor?I know that Sherry fans represent the scorned group of Kant supporters. Know this: this same group unknowingly let Kant and company get away with #*#*# , *€€£% as long as they hugged them on the street and asked them, “how’s your mother!”But make NO MISTAKE Kant and company were in these positions because they were PAID to be there. Sherry was PAID good money to DEDICATE her life to living Fairhope. Heck, if I had been paid that much, so would I and so would you.So please consider the positive changes that Karin has made, despite the ugliness and less than decent treatment she has received.In spite of their powerful and cruel opposition, Mayor Wilson has: balance the budget, made infrastructure improvements and has the plans waiting to be approved to continue, written and received grants for infrastructure, received grants for ongoing projects, been fair to all people, created a city marina is now run by the City along with capital improvements made- just to name a few- promises made promises keptSupporting Karin Wilson for a job well done !<wp:post_name><![CDATA[fly-on-the-wall]]>
</wp:post_name>
<wp:post_name><![CDATA[oil-slick]]>
</wp:post_name>	wp:meta_value><![CDATA[6831]]></wp:meta_value>
<wp:meta_value><![CDATA[It defies logic that a former BP executive is going to lecture Fairhope citizens about contamination of the Mobile Bay.]]></wp:meta_value>
		Hey Manelos...you made a mistake.
<wp:post_name><![CDATA[scary]]>
</wp:post_name>
<wp:meta_value><![CDATA[6849]]></wp:meta_value>
<wp:meta_value><![CDATA[Some really weird and scary things are going on in Fairhope.]]></wp:meta_value>

CATALYST recently lost the First Congressional Race to Mr Jerry Carl. This was a victory for the citizens of Baldwin County. Please help, VOTE, in your municipal election in Baldwin County AUG. 25th.https://rippreport.com/2020/07/17/catalyst-ass-whoopin/<wp:post_name><![CDATA[catalyst-aka-scott-boone-consulting]]>
</wp:post_name>
End Wasteful Spending &amp; Restore Fiscal HealthFour years ago, the city was running an annual $6 Million deficit, making payments on millions of dollars of debt, and requiring most of the profits from our Utility department to subsidize its budget.Today, the City is fiscally self-reliant, paid off long-term debt, increased combined City/Utility cash funds by almost 60% leaving our gas, electric, water and wastewater utilities the ability to finally afford its long-ignored maintenance and upgrade needs.In addition, my administration obtained $18M in RESTORE funds, most of which will be invested in sewer system upgrades and a sewer overflow prevention plan along the Eastern Shore - money citizens will save in sewer rate increases.This is what fiscal responsibility looks like and will continue under my leadership as a fiscal conservative with ~30 years experience in Finance &amp; Business Management.This is a promise - like the ones I made in 2016 for which I delivered. Let’s stay the course moving forward together.<style><wp:post_name><![CDATA[nappi-award]]>
</wp:post_name>
<wp:meta_value><![CDATA[6856]]></wp:meta_value>
<wp:meta_value><![CDATA[The Mayor of Fairhope has won four years in a row, The Nappi Award for the hardest working elected city official...]]></wp:meta_value>
<wp:meta_value><![CDATA[https://cdn.rippreport.com/wp-content/uploads/2020/08/cropped-karin1.jpg]]></wp:meta_value>
<wp:meta_value><![CDATA[6857]]></wp:meta_value>
	We either get a hard worker who cares about Fairhope or we get a Catalyst who just wants to allow Catalyst to sell this town out
CATALYST/Scott Boone and the current Mayor of Daphne are picking your next Mayor and City Council members for you. DO NOT VOTE FOR ANY CSB CANDIDATES.Signs in Spanish Fort and Bay Minette are all the same style pvc framed CATALYST/Scott Boone signs, manufactured at the same place.In the next two weeks you will hear of signs missing destroyed or damaged, none of them will be CATALYST/Scott Boone signs. In Fairhope it is already going on, they have perfected the art of sign disappearance in Fairhope. In the 2016 Fairhope election a man was caught with a pickup full of signs, all were signs of those opposing the status quo.Use your eyes to see, use your brain to think.<wp:post_name><![CDATA[catalyst-signs]]>
</wp:post_name>
<wp:meta_value><![CDATA[6882]]></wp:meta_value>
<wp:meta_value><![CDATA[Study the signs and their locations. Notice how CSB candidates signs all are the same, pvc framed. CSG uses signs as their number one tool in elections.]]></wp:meta_value>

<wp:post_name><![CDATA[howell-gibbens]]>
</wp:post_name>
<wp:meta_value><![CDATA[6893]]></wp:meta_value>
<wp:meta_value><![CDATA[The explosive growth that Fairhope has been experiencing has not just overloaded our infrastructure it has put strains on our community...]]></wp:meta_value>
			I await them for eternal absolution
<wp:post_name><![CDATA[catalyst-attack]]>
</wp:post_name>
<wp:meta_value><![CDATA[6897]]></wp:meta_value>
<wp:meta_value><![CDATA[If you live in Baldwin County, please share this post as much as possible. This is very IMPORTANT.]]></wp:meta_value>
	Burrell, Boone and Brown all win with almost identical 68% victory. Carey wins with no runoff. 
<wp:post_name><![CDATA[catalyst-bullies]]>
</wp:post_name>
<wp:post_name><![CDATA[questions-for-fairhope]]>
</wp:post_name>
In 2020, I am again backing Mayor Wilson who deserves another term to finish many of the projects started in the first term.If you are a teacher you must have a college education to teach, just like many professions. Education is important in our society. As we speak, our teachers are working especially hard to educate our children. It is driven in every child’s head that education counts.Fairhope has 4 candidates running for Mayor, 3 with college degrees, one, Sullivan, with a high school education.Let’s not FORGET the Oil Slick candidate. The “good Vibes” BP guy on the paddle board, who wants you to forget the BP Oil Spill and the corruption it spawned in Fairhope. Just mellow and have “good Vibes”, forget the corruption, that is the message written on the paddle board.Our Former Mayor and former State Senator, while Sullivan was employed, stole 639,000 dollars of BP grant money.Most of all let’s not forget “good vibes” pledge not to have anything to do with CATALYST. We will see if he is covered in oil or clean on Aug. 26th.https://rippreport.com/2020/07/29/oil-slick/Mayor Wilson has a degree in finance, is a small business owner, where she has made good use of the degree for 25 years. Mayor Wilson has also been Mayor for 4 grueling years subjected to bullying, lying and deceit, delivered by a CATALYST council.https://rippreport.com/2020/08/05/catalyst-aka-scott-boone-consulting/The citizens of Fairhope had better use their education and decide on a Mayor with experience and education.Sullivan was fired in 2017 since then she has had three jobs and resigned from the last one.Sullivan proudly represents Catalyst, who is sponsoring her, and her get even attitude will certainly result in multiple firings in city hall. if elected. Since 2016, she has worked for the city, an internet company, Foley Main Street and most recently, Riviera Utilities, where she resigned. One job a year for 4 years? Think about that.Mayor Wilson, who has had the same job for 4 years, reversed an annual 6 million dollar debt to fiscal health. Increased city and utility cash funds 59.18%: 17 million. Paid off city long term debt and paid down utility debt 33%. The Mayor obtained 23 million in grants and restoration funds. The Mayor also introduced responsible growth objectives and came up with a infrastructure revitalization plan, without borrowing money. She also increased dramatically overall citizen engagement. Her accomplishments were rewarded with 4 Nappi Awards, For The Hardest Working Elected Official on the Eastern Shore.CATALYST and the three B's have never received any awards.https://rippreport.com/2020/08/06/nappi-award/The thing that has this election so hot is that Mayor Wilson, in addition to the above, Scrutinized, Identified and Eliminated wasteful contractors. She successfully stopped the majority of corruption within city hall. These wasteful contractors represent CATALYST, who has been supported by the three B’s, Burrell Boone and Brown. They want control and they want Sullivan to carry the water.Re- electing the 3 B’s and electing a high school graduate, who is a fired employee of the city, that sued the city, without ever explaining why, is “GOING BACKWARDS”. Use your education to determine the best EDUCATED and QUALIFIED candidates. This is a Municipal election not a popularity contest.Study the signs in Fairhope, CATALYST/ Scott Boone candidates all have their signs together, they want a CATALYST block vote. If you have a Catalyst Mayor and a Catalyst council you are guaranteed corruption. Think how stupid this is: CATALYST is run by councilman Boone’s son, Scott, talk about an inside deal!https://rippreport.com/2020/08/07/catalyst-signs/The three incumbent city councilmen, 3 B’s, also face challengers next week. Jack Burrell, Robert Brown and Kevin Boone will face Deb Hokpkins, Howell Gibbens and Joshua Gammon on the ballot, respectively.Hopkins, Gibbens, and Gammon represent new fresh candidates with no ties to CATALYST. The Fairhope City Council will have the opportunity to rid itself of CATALYST and the self serving B’s.A special on the CATALYST three B’s and their accumulative corruption while in office will be featured soon.<wp:post_name><![CDATA[fairhope-going-backwards]]>
</wp:post_name>
<wp:meta_value><![CDATA[6926]]></wp:meta_value>
<wp:meta_value><![CDATA[Hopkins, Gibbens, and Gammon represent new fresh candidates with no ties to CATALYST. City Council will have the opportunity to rid itself of CATALYST.]]></wp:meta_value>

<wp:post_name><![CDATA[fairhope-voters-guide]]>
</wp:post_name>
<wp:meta_value><![CDATA[6929]]></wp:meta_value>
	wp:meta_value><![CDATA[We still believe that Fairhope is a special place worth fighting for. If you share these concerns, and value your home, your property...]]></wp:meta_value>

<wp:post_name><![CDATA[catalyst-missing-in-action]]>
</wp:post_name>
With all due respect, I will not respond to comments. Thank you for the love & prayers, stay safe & keep on smiling.....I love you all ❤️????<wp:post_name><![CDATA[women-stand-together]]>
</wp:post_name>
<wp:post_name><![CDATA[catalyst-council-lawsuits]]>
</wp:post_name>
<wp:meta_value><![CDATA[6951]]></wp:meta_value>
<wp:meta_value><![CDATA[When the triangle lawsuit was going on, Fairhope's insurance company, sued the city saying that the city's bad decisions led to the lawsuit...]]></wp:meta_value>

<wp:post_name><![CDATA[fairhopes-golden-key]]>
</wp:post_name>
<wp:post_name><![CDATA[absolute-power]]>
</wp:post_name>
<wp:post_name><![CDATA[baldwin-county]]>
</wp:post_name>
<wp:meta_value><![CDATA[6961]]></wp:meta_value>
<wp:meta_value><![CDATA[If you live in Baldwin County then you know that local news print is almost non existent. Citizens are at a disadvantage at knowing what the real truth is...]]></wp:meta_value>

<wp:post_name><![CDATA[shadow-government-southern-style]]>
</wp:post_name>
<wp:meta_value><![CDATA[6966]]></wp:meta_value>

<wp:post_name><![CDATA[backstory-podcast-9-11-2001-remembered]]>
</wp:post_name>
Review of Shadow Government: Southern StyleBy Thomas GallionChris E. WarnerSeptember 15, 2020<wp:post_name><![CDATA[reading-in-the-rain]]>
</wp:post_name>
<wp:meta_value><![CDATA[6973]]></wp:meta_value>
<wp:meta_value><![CDATA[You're stuck inside. How about doing a little reading? It may educate you on why Alabama is number one, in corruption and religion, in the United States.]]></wp:meta_value>

<wp:post_name><![CDATA[backstory-podcast-no-54-trump-positive]]>
</wp:post_name>
<wp:meta_value><![CDATA[34,353,000 SARS&#x2d;COV&#x2d;2 cases globally with 1,023,000 deaths. The USA has the highest rate of infection of any country on earth]]></wp:meta_value>
<wp:meta_value><![CDATA[6970]]></wp:meta_value>

MIN:34:15 to MIN: 38:15The council and the city attorney remained mute, not even passing gas, when asked about when the McSharry assault charges would be filed.https://rippreport.com/2020/08/22/women-stand-together/Last week at council meeting, during public participation, Johnathan Lucia complained about the Fly Creek Apartments being flooded, something that was predicted years ago. If you live in Fairhope then you are aware of how controversial the apartments have been. Council President Burrell blew Mr Lucia better than Sally. Burrell played dumb, which was easy, and passed the buck to the City Attorney and current Mayor. It has been reported that Burrell has been boasting that he will remain Council President, as he has for 8 years, and that he will be the next Mayor in 2024. Here we go again.https://youtu.be/_VcXYeVh6UY<wp:post_name><![CDATA[m-i-a]]>
</wp:post_name>
<wp:post_name><![CDATA[missed-the-bullet]]>
</wp:post_name>
<wp:meta_value><![CDATA[6982]]></wp:meta_value>
<wp:meta_value><![CDATA[Sally kicked Baldwin County’s ass, however we missed the Delta bullet.]]></wp:meta_value>
	Haygood says he did not run because God told him to do other things.
<wp:post_name><![CDATA[backstory-podcast-55]]>
</wp:post_name>
<wp:meta_value><![CDATA[6987]]></wp:meta_value>
<wp:meta_value><![CDATA[Yes we have had so many hurricanes this season that we ran out of names and are using the Greek alphabet, this storm will be known as Hurricane Delta 2020]]></wp:meta_value>

<wp:post_name><![CDATA[slap-in-the-face]]>
</wp:post_name>
<wp:meta_value><![CDATA[6990]]></wp:meta_value>
<wp:meta_value><![CDATA[Baldwin County citizens have just been slapped in the face. Want to know why Alabama is number one in corruption and the butt of jokes?]]></wp:meta_value>

<wp:post_name><![CDATA[bsp-tlp]]>
</wp:post_name>
<wp:post_name><![CDATA[on-vacation]]>
</wp:post_name>
<wp:meta_value><![CDATA[6997]]></wp:meta_value>

<wp:post_name><![CDATA[queen-bee]]>
</wp:post_name>
<wp:meta_value><![CDATA[The queen bee is getting a $112,000 salary boost per year above former Mayor Wilson’s salary. That brings the Queen Bee’s salary and benefits to $160,000 a year.]]></wp:meta_value>

<wp:post_name><![CDATA[backstory-podcast-58-the-rushin-prognostication]]>
</wp:post_name>
<wp:meta_value><![CDATA[6970]]></wp:meta_value>

<wp:post_name><![CDATA[backstory-podcast-the-46th-president-of-the-united-states]]>
</wp:post_name>
<wp:meta_value><![CDATA[The Media Companies/News Outlets are confident and have called the 2020 Presidential Election for Joseph Robinette Biden Jr.]]></wp:meta_value>

<wp:post_name><![CDATA[semper-fi-veterans-day]]>
</wp:post_name>	wp:meta_value><![CDATA[SEMPER FI / VETERANS DAY]]></wp:meta_value>
<wp:meta_value><![CDATA[November 10th is the Marine Corp Birthday and November 11th is Veterans Day. On these two days I always reflect on my fathers career in the Army]]></wp:meta_value>

<wp:post_name><![CDATA[take-a-chance]]>
</wp:post_name>
<wp:meta_value><![CDATA[“TAKE A CHANCE”]]></wp:meta_value>
<wp:meta_key><![CDATA[email]]></wp:meta_key><wp:meta_key><![CDATA[comment]]></wp:meta_key><wp:meta_value><![CDATA[no]]></wp:meta_value>
<wp:meta_key><![CDATA[options]]></wp:meta_key><wp:meta_value><![CDATA[0]]></wp:meta_value>

<wp:post_name><![CDATA[howling-rains-passing-gas]]>
</wp:post_name>
<wp:post_name><![CDATA[jackass-jack]]>
</wp:post_name>
<wp:meta_value><![CDATA[The Mayor of Fairhope and the City Council got hammered by the public, medical professionals and first responders over the city’s decision to have a large...]]></wp:meta_value>

<wp:post_name><![CDATA[dollars-and-lives]]>
</wp:post_name>
<wp:meta_value><![CDATA[https://cdn.rippreport.com/wp-content/uploads/2020/12/cropped-dollars1.jpg]]></wp:meta_value>
<wp:meta_value><![CDATA[The City of Fairhope’s 6.2 million dollar waterfront project became a political hot potato during the last municipal election. Politicians put their feet in their mouths and now are trying...]]></wp:meta_value>

<wp:post_name><![CDATA[battle-of-weeks-family]]>
</wp:post_name>wp:meta_value><![CDATA[All of us have read news articles that have driven us up the wall, but this article and story is insane and most likely a perfect example of someone with power]]></wp:meta_value>

"People see Fairhope as a flourishing utopia where people build bigger and bigger houses, with a boat, the perfect kids and the perfect life. Fairhope’s prosperity and perfect surface is a veneer that covers deeper problems. But there is something darker underneath the veneer. Under the surface of Fairhope, more families struggle than we want to admit or imagine. Some people are hurting, getting left behind and forgotten."<wp:post_name><![CDATA[alabama-corruption-insurance]]>
</wp:post_name>
<wp:meta_value><![CDATA[Why is Alabama so corrupt? Because all the Alabama government agencies or elected officials refuse to do their jobs.]]></wp:meta_value>

<wp:post_name><![CDATA[backstory-podcast-no-64-300000-dead]]>
</wp:post_name>
<wp:post_name><![CDATA[happy-new-year-3]]>
</wp:post_name>Trump Pardons 50 plus, we break down the worst.What's hidden in the Coronavirus Relief Bill (from amberjack counting in the Gulf to the creation of a Copyright Claims Board)? Russia hacked half of corporate America and most of the Government, why no coverage?  Justice Lyn Stuart was given the Howell Heflin Award.  As goes Georgia so goes the Senate, runoff January 6, 2021.  Dr. Robert Bentley got the vaccine to the amusement of no one.  The Nashville Christmas Day bombing tragedy (5G) and The Pope's new Instagram Bikini Model pal.
<wp:post_name><![CDATA[backstory-podcast-no-65-happy-new-year-goodbye-2020]]>
</wp:post_name>	
<wp:post_name><![CDATA[alabama-suicide]]>
</wp:post_name>
<wp:meta_value><![CDATA[ALABAMA SUICIDE]]></wp:meta_value>
<wp:meta_value><![CDATA[Georgia elects two Democrats as Senators and the balance of power in Washington shifts from red to blue. The President gets all the credit for their success...]]></wp:meta_value>

Instead, our president decided to go the other way and incite and antagonize.  And our cities burn.  What's your solution?  Kill them all?  Imprison millions?There's nothing good about any riot.	<wp:post_name><![CDATA[a-long-strange-day-jan-6-2021]]>
</wp:post_name>
<wp:meta_value><![CDATA[A recap of the events and consequences of the Storming of the US Capitol Building, we will flesh it out on Backstory Podcast No 66.]]></wp:meta_value>
<wp:meta_value><![CDATA[6970]]></wp:meta_value>
I agree completely. Your friends and family probably feel the same way you do.  Who brings up politics? Technology moved too fast.  I think all sides are confused and diverging from reality. People are fed endless counterpoints and snarky phrases. People are lazy, why study for the test if all the best answers are at your fingertips? Why look into anything when I have this great snarky counterpoint handed right to me?All the while, everyone ignores what their "side" is doing.  For every poor decision, there's another poor decision that the other side made, so it's all good."We see other countries going Socialist and collapsing, but it seems like a great plan to us."
<wp:post_name><![CDATA[quarterback-sneak]]>
</wp:post_name>
<wp:post_name><![CDATA[winner-and-loser]]>
</wp:post_name>	wp:meta_value><![CDATA[Congratulations Nick Saban and the Alabama Football team, you have made Alabama proud. Saban is successful because of Leadership, Ethics, Transparency and above all PRINCIPAL.]]></wp:meta_value>

<wp:post_name><![CDATA[the-big-lie-%f0%9f%a4%a5]]>
</wp:post_name>	wp:meta_value><![CDATA[THE BIG LIE ?]]></wp:meta_value>
<wp:meta_value><![CDATA[Vietnam Veterans were lied to by our politicians. 1968 was the year Martin Luther King was assassinated. The same year Robert Kennedy was assassinated.]]></wp:meta_value>

<wp:post_name><![CDATA[redneck-renovations]]>
</wp:post_name>
<wp:meta_value><![CDATA[redneck-repairs]]></wp:meta_value>

<wp:post_name><![CDATA[secret-society]]>
</wp:post_name>
<wp:meta_value><![CDATA[A secret society is a club or an organization whose activities, events, inner functioning, or membership are concealed from non&#x2d;members.]]></wp:meta_value>

<wp:post_name><![CDATA[super-bowl-lv]]>
</wp:post_name>
<wp:meta_value><![CDATA[Super Bowl LV, the 55th Super Bowl and the 51st modern&#x2d;era National Football League championship game, will decide the league champion for the 2020 NFL season.]]></wp:meta_value>

<wp:post_name><![CDATA[non-lethal]]>
</wp:post_name>
<wp:meta_value><![CDATA[The citizens of Baldwin County have 14 municipalities, with police departments and a sheriff’s department. For the most part they do a very good job of protect]]></wp:meta_value>
	I say to the police that if you want a George Floyd incident here in Baldwin County then go for it
The Senate concluded arguments in the Impeachment of Former-President Donald John Trump today, for the second time. Brandenburg vs Ohio was the case on point and was mostly ignored- defining a 3 prong test for when speech is not protected. Spoiler Alert: The protagonist is a Klansman. In short, The Senate should have called witnesses. The Lagniappe Mobile Newspaper takes aim at a number of issues- vaccine eligibility changes, The Mobile River Bridge and Bayway Project is back and Fairhope Councilman and Eastern Shore MPO Chairman Jack Burrell “the Great Negotiator” is right out front, controversy surrounding a firing range near Foley, Alabama, and and article about Who will run now that Senator Richard Shelby is retiring?And who will bring home the bacon? Tubbs? Bay Minette lands $200K for AR-15’s, an IR Drone, a Humvee, and Covert Surveillance Equipment (not a dime for taser shotguns). The Alabama Legislature is back in session without an audience so we tell you about the Bad Bills to watch. Growth is always a difficult subject but the Golden Triangle project in Baldwin County near Stapleton, actually mostly in Spanish Fort Planning Jurisdiction, is a huge project (4,200 Acres with 12,000 residences and 1.5 Million Sq Ft of commercial space; and we discuss the reason the land was undeveloped until now. AG Steve Marshall announced a $60M settlement with Terminix. Not one person is going to jail for violation of the Alabama Deceptive Trade Practices Act. And Larry Flynt, arch nemesis of The Reverend Jerry Falwell, died yesterday. He was an unlikely Free Speech Icon and the world is a poorer place because of his passing. And for good measure we throw in some Baldwin County History that may blow your little minds.<wp:post_name><![CDATA[backstory-podcast-senate-impeachment]]>
</wp:post_name>		Maybe this democracy thing is not viable after all			EXPAND MEDICAID, sounds simple, practical and in the best interest of all Alabama citizens. Only one obstacle Medicaid is part of the Affordable Care Act.Let’s go back to Love Gov. Bentley in 2015 when he left 3 BILLION DOLLARS, on the table and threw heath care, under the table. Bentley was a doctor but he was focused on being the Luv Gov.
<wp:post_name><![CDATA[insanity-2]]>
</wp:post_name>
<wp:meta_value><![CDATA[INSANITY]]></wp:meta_value>
<wp:meta_value><![CDATA[Alabama needs a psychiatrist and a financial advisor. The lives lost, hospitals closed and billions of dollars, left on the table, is the result of despicable..]]></wp:meta_value>
<wp:meta_value><![CDATA[https://cdn.rippreport.com/wp-content/uploads/2021/02/4e441113-cropped-97a4d175-w3ktnqtrzbbolfwyejy3vur3mq.jpg]]></wp:meta_value>

<wp:post_name><![CDATA[i-quit]]>
</wp:post_name>
<wp:post_name><![CDATA[honeymoon]]>
</wp:post_name>
<wp:post_name><![CDATA[selected-not-elected]]>
</wp:post_name>
<wp:post_name><![CDATA[csb-railroad-nomination]]>
</wp:post_name>	
<wp:post_name><![CDATA[backstory-podcast-no-75-a-year-of-plague]]>
</wp:post_name>This is nothing new. In fact it is quite common. Only this time it was publicly documented. Four of the council sat on the last council. They were the least productive, obstructive and corrupt of any council that has ever represented Fairhope.https://rippreport.com/2018/10/19/loser/The Ripp Report is a Non-Profit Consumer Organization. The Ripp Report handles consumer issues, offers consultation on specific issues, family court issues and exposes political corruption. We cannot give legal advice, as we are not attorneys. We can however assist in finding competent attorneys. The intent of our non-profit is to inform the public on numerous issues, political and non political.What they did with the council appointment was unethical and a deliberate effort on the council’s part to eliminate public participation. A federal lawsuit is evidence, and a precedent, to the council’s history of suppressing free speech and making a mockery of Public Participation.https://rippreport.com/2021/03/12/csb-railroad-nomination/“Without any public participation the Fairhope City Council President, Jack Burrell, decided who would be the next councilperson and publicly declared that, “I made the decision.”This week the Fauxhope city attorney, Marcus McDowell represented Paula DiNardi in a case that was suppose to be an assault and intoxication charge against Ronan McSharry, owner of McSharry’s bar in Fairhope.This has been a high profile case and another failure of the city attorney, city council and municipal judge. McSharry, already on probation, had help from the city attorney who, conveniently and repeatedly, failed to file the assault charge leaving McSharry with only having to face an intoxication charge in circuit court. The judicial hand off to a Judge that “wanted” the case.Judge Stankowski, after a one day trial where McSharry was found guilty, rendering a sentence of one year, unsupervised probation, without addressing the assault charge or the fact McSharry had already been sentenced to 6 months in jail and was on probation at the time of the assault on DiNardi.I was asked as a public observer in the court room, not a fact witness, to leave the court room. I was not summons to court, however when the trial began and after opening statements, witnesses were asked to wait outside the courtroom to be called. That is when attorneys asked the Judge to expel me from the court as they “MAY” call me as a witness. This was done to keep me out of the court room.
<wp:post_name><![CDATA[boycott-mcsharrys]]>
</wp:post_name>
<wp:post_name><![CDATA[backstory-podcast-no-76-a-plague-of-apathy]]>
</wp:post_name>		
<wp:post_name><![CDATA[a-slap-on-the-wrist]]>
</wp:post_name>
https://lagniappemobile.com/fairhope-city-council-to-consider-bayfront-park-improvements/Howell Raines, who was a vocal critic of the previous plan, said this one also doesn’t pass muster.<wp:post_name><![CDATA[got-fleas]]>
</wp:post_name>	Make him howl at the jubilee moon!	
<wp:post_name><![CDATA[southern-gothic]]>
</wp:post_name>	like I become a car  sitting in my garage?Cry for Baldwin County.  This was once God’s country but SBC has enabled it to be Satan’s Spawn
https://rippreport.com/2021/01/11/quarterback-sneak/In Fairhope, the quarterback is none other than the most sneaky and corrupt politician in Baldwin County. The great negotiator, Sneaky Jack Burrell, who chose tonight to use the City Council meeting, which no-one goes to, to swear in the Municipal Judge Haymes Snedeker.https://rippreport.com/2021/04/01/got-fleas/In a letter to Sullivan and Council President Jack Burrell last week, Raines expressed concern the proposal will not be fully vetted by citizens prior to council approval.https://rippreport.com/2021/03/12/csb-railroad-nomination/The council denies they knew anything about Robert Brown purchasing his ”family” property July 21 2020. Once it was made public and on the record, Council President Burrell got all tongue tied trying to defend his railroad nomination process. He contradicts himself numerous times and ends up with one of his episodes of gibberish.https://rippreport.com/2021/03/07/selected-not-elected/The Fairhope Mayor and acting Mayor Burrell are moving at lightning speed to replace Robert Brown’s seat on the City Council, before any citizens can say a word.https://rippreport.com/2021/03/26/a-slap-on-the-wrist/The City attorney, Marcus McDowell, works for the council, Jack Burrell controls the council. McSharry is, or was, Jack’s closest friend. Fairhope councilman “Strawman” Kevin Boone is the father of Scott Boone and the conduit to SBC, this is a very cozy and politically connected Cabal.<wp:post_name><![CDATA[no-radar]]>
</wp:post_name>Fairhope remains the number one place to retire in the ??.The Fairhope Single Tax built this town.
<wp:post_name><![CDATA[backstory-podcast-no-79-ole-peg-gy]]>
</wp:post_name>		
<wp:post_name><![CDATA[backstory-podcast-no-81-tan-rested-ready]]>
</wp:post_name>
<wp:meta_value><![CDATA[Mr. Ripp has been out of the Country and gives us the 411 on travel out of the Country during Covid&#x2d;19 and the Immunization Passport.]]></wp:meta_value>

<wp:post_name><![CDATA[backstory-podcast-special-legislative-alert-alabama-medical-cannabis]]>
</wp:post_name>	wp:meta_value><![CDATA[Backstory Podcast Special Legislative Alert: Alabama Medical Cannabis]]></wp:meta_value>
<wp:meta_value><![CDATA[The Alabama House of Representatives has passed SB 46 establishing a statewide medical marijuana program. The bill now heads back to Senate for final approval.]]></wp:meta_value>
The city has abandoned that idea. “because there is no evidence of any such pattern of misconduct, which is a necessary precondition for a finding of deliberate indifference.”The problem for Sheriff Mack is that he has a well established pattern, and conduct, of “deliberate indifference. The sheriff department has two more cases climbing the legal ladder where loss of life by the hands of the sheriff’s office has demonstrated “deliberate indifference”.For years the Baldwin County Sheriff Office, headed by Hoss Mack has hidden behind Qualified Immunity and has avoided any accountability. In 2022 Hoss may retire, let’s hope so. If he does not retire he will face a lot of public scrutiny.https://lagniappemobile.com/judge-blisters-hoss-and-hunady-in-victor-death/{Lagniappe articles may have a paywall} Online subscriptions are available as well as free weekly copies in news stands.For 8 months, The Ripp Report has been working on a case involving the Baldwin County Sheriff and will soon go public with a story that should disturb every citizen in Alabama. This particular case demonstrates what a poor judicial system exists Baldwin County as well as shines a lot of light on Sheriff Hoss Mack.https://lagniappemobile.com/adem-holds-public-hearing-on-plant-barry-coal-ash-pond/The only other news or lack of news is the Coal Ash Pond at Berry Steam Plant. Alabama Power keeps telling the general public not to worry. I guess they forgot about the BP spill. They need that Alabama Power contribution money for the next election.
<wp:post_name><![CDATA[s-o-s]]>
</wp:post_name>wp:meta_value><![CDATA[First the Fairhope Waterfront project has been getting progressively worse. What started out as a citizen driven grant has turned into a political hot potato. The project has been whittled down to a stub.]]></wp:meta_value>
	See Ripp?  It is good - Damned good - that you are back!  So many of us were suffering withdrawal symptoms with you being gone.  When you are not there, you are missed.
<wp:post_name><![CDATA[weasel-contractor]]>
</wp:post_name>	wp:meta_value><![CDATA[Baldwin County really made a mistake when they elected Chris Elliott to replace Tripp Boom Boom Pittman as State Senator.]]></wp:meta_value>

<wp:post_name><![CDATA[tiny-steps]]>
</wp:post_name>
<wp:meta_value><![CDATA[The last session of the Alabama Legislature took tiny steps when it comes to accomplishing any real serious issues plaguing the state. Prisons, health care’ medicaid” and the gambling bill all wound up in the trash can.]]></wp:meta_value>

Please attend the June 10th meeting and support Hawthorne Glen residents. Be sure to wear high boots the shi- is going to be deep.<wp:post_name><![CDATA[no-qualifications]]>
</wp:post_name>			
<wp:post_name><![CDATA[pied-piper]]>
</wp:post_name><wp:meta_key><![CDATA[email]]></wp:meta_key><wp:meta_key><![CDATA[comment]]></wp:meta_key><wp:meta_value><![CDATA[0]]></wp:meta_value>
<wp:meta_key><![CDATA[options]]></wp:meta_key><wp:meta_value><![CDATA[0]]></wp:meta_value>

<wp:post_name><![CDATA[i-10-toll-bridge-state]]>
</wp:post_name>	Back in the 1970's and 1980's the Wallace Tunnels were power washed almost every night and kept clean and pristine.  Now, they are dirty because the tunnels are not being cleaned as often.  Why not?  The state will tell you to save money.  The state will hire a six figure bureaucrat and then take the money from cleaning to pay his or her expense.  What a shame.
<wp:post_name><![CDATA[double-red-flags-faux-hope]]>
</wp:post_name>
<wp:meta_value><![CDATA[DOUBLE RED FLAGS at the beach this weekend. Rip&#x2d;currents rough seas and high water. The same can be said about Faux&#x2d;Hope. Red flags are going up faster than the American flag on July 4th.]]></wp:meta_value>
<wp:meta_key><![CDATA[email]]></wp:meta_key><wp:meta_key><![CDATA[comment]]></wp:meta_key><wp:meta_value><![CDATA[no]]></wp:meta_value>
<wp:meta_key><![CDATA[options]]></wp:meta_key><wp:meta_value><![CDATA[0]]></wp:meta_value>

<wp:post_name><![CDATA[live-like-a-coward-die-like-a-coward]]>
</wp:post_name><wp:meta_key><![CDATA[email]]></wp:meta_key><wp:meta_key><![CDATA[comment]]></wp:meta_key><wp:meta_value><![CDATA[0]]></wp:meta_value>
<wp:meta_key><![CDATA[options]]></wp:meta_key><wp:meta_value><![CDATA[0]]></wp:meta_value>

Jack has said “he is opposed to federal assistance, however, if it was offered he would take the money.”“Obviously, there’s going to be a toll. We don’t know what that toll is going to look like right now. I think it’s going to be a small toll. But I do think as a passenger vehicle, if you choose to use the bridge, you will pay a toll. But we will maintain those legacy routes.”It is obvious that the politicians and supporters of the bridge have actually fallen off the bridge. They are stepping all over themselves trying to be conservative to a fault. They cannot build a bridge without federal money, which many feel should be all federal money.The state of Alabama cannot fund the bridge. It cannot even provide for education, prisons or healthcare. The revenue streams of other states have been ignored by Alabama.The lottery and legalization of marijuana is providing neighboring states billions while Alabama is going to “study” whether it is feasible. Alabama left $3.2 billion on the table, not participating in Medicaid, further deteriorating an already fractured state wide medical system.Those yelling the loudest about the bridge are more interested in development than traffic. The politicians listed on this page ensure failure.<wp:post_name><![CDATA[no-mo-bridge]]>
</wp:post_name><wp:meta_key><![CDATA[email]]></wp:meta_key><wp:meta_key><![CDATA[comment]]></wp:meta_key><wp:meta_value><![CDATA[0]]></wp:meta_value>
<wp:meta_key><![CDATA[options]]></wp:meta_key><wp:meta_value><![CDATA[0]]></wp:meta_value>

The Ripp Report will keep you updated as to where and when you need to bring your wheelbarrow for free manure provided by the Director of the Ethics Commission, who personally will shovel you a “load”.Mr. Albritton should resign immediately.<wp:post_name><![CDATA[alabama-ethics-self-dealing-immunity]]>
</wp:post_name><wp:meta_key><![CDATA[email]]></wp:meta_key><wp:meta_key><![CDATA[comment]]></wp:meta_key><wp:meta_value><![CDATA[0]]></wp:meta_value>
<wp:meta_key><![CDATA[options]]></wp:meta_key><wp:meta_value><![CDATA[0]]></wp:meta_value>
<wp:meta_value><![CDATA[alabama-ethics-%e2%86%92-self-dealing-%e2%86%92-immunity]]></wp:meta_value>

<wp:post_name><![CDATA[happy-fourth-of-july]]>
</wp:post_name><wp:meta_key><![CDATA[email]]></wp:meta_key><wp:meta_key><![CDATA[comment]]></wp:meta_key>	wp:meta_key><![CDATA[options]]></wp:meta_key><wp:meta_value><![CDATA[0]]></wp:meta_value>

What can you do?Write a letter call the TV and Radio stations and ask why they are not covering the self dealing self stealing, Mr Tom Albritton, Director of the Alabama Ethics Commission.<wp:post_name><![CDATA[self-dealing-self-stealing]]>
</wp:post_name>
<wp:meta_value><![CDATA[Self Dealing is the same as self stealing. Mr. Albritton children got more scholarship money than the relatives of Mabel Amos.]]></wp:meta_value>
<wp:meta_value><![CDATA[https://cdn.rippreport.com/b2bf2e93-cropped-0390ec1b-ethics-commission-al.jpg]]></wp:meta_value>

<b>Lagniappe subscription not required.</b>Mr. Albritton, one of three trustees of the Mabel Amos Memorial Fund, is also an attorney. He is well aware of self dealing and the Internal Revenue Codes related to self dealing and taxable expenditures.Albrittion’s children have received scholarships, valued at 105,000 dollars, from the fund.The Ripp Report has filed a separate, Alabama Bar Complaint against Mr Tom Albritton.<wp:post_name><![CDATA[writ-of-mandamus-and-bar-complaint]]>
</wp:post_name>
<wp:meta_value><![CDATA[https://cdn.rippreport.com/ed7ee5d2-cropped-d6b15712-docs.png]]></wp:meta_value>

<wp:post_name><![CDATA[letter-to-the-alabama-attorney-general]]>
</wp:post_name>
<wp:meta_value><![CDATA[Dear Sir: During the last election cycle I had the pleasure of talking with you in Fairhope Alabama, during one of your campaign stops. I explained to you the level of corruption in Baldwin County and how the Alabama Ethics Commission was not investigating ethics complaints.]]></wp:meta_value>
<wp:meta_value><![CDATA[https://cdn.rippreport.com/7e8a1579-cropped-0b48367c-ripp-stamp.jpg]]></wp:meta_value>
			Dismissed Councilman Robert Brown's personal benefit with ESAC remodel as a committee member.Dismissed Counvilman Kevin Boone's complaint for his LLCs benefiting from planning aprrovals as planning commissioner.When will these docile voters wake up?	Are they not able to quote the email's context and highlight/bold the points they are making?I am now in my 2nd year of monthly payments to the Baldwin Co court system because of the corruption between them and the audit division. Quick reminder but they got me on a sales tax issue that did not apply to my event based biz which had no durable exchange of goods.
<wp:post_name><![CDATA[obituary]]>
</wp:post_name>
<wp:meta_value><![CDATA[Frances (Fran) J. Neumann of Daphne, Alabama, passed away unexpectedly on Monday, June 28, 2021 from natural causes. She was ninety&#x2d;three going on a hundred, her oft&#x2d;expressed goal.]]></wp:meta_value>
<wp:meta_value><![CDATA[https://cdn.rippreport.com/35c7af12-cropped-524ffa54-obt.jpg]]></wp:meta_value>

<wp:post_name><![CDATA[backstory-podcast-no-92-a-vintage-year]]>
</wp:post_name>
<wp:post_name><![CDATA[striking-oil]]>
</wp:post_name>wp:meta_value><![CDATA[https://cdn.rippreport.com/97592baa-cropped-59f6643e-regions-bank-fb.png]]></wp:meta_value>

<wp:post_name><![CDATA[license-to-steal]]>
</wp:post_name>
<wp:meta_value><![CDATA[https://cdn.rippreport.com/d2aa1744-cropped-882e04bb-alabama-ethics-commission-fb.jpg]]></wp:meta_value>
Tail wagging dog.
<wp:post_name><![CDATA[mega-lost-opportunity]]>
</wp:post_name>	Baldwin County Economic Alliance exists to pay Lee to talk about stats and travel expense. Lee takes money from local government and federal grants for self benefit with little benefit to the taxpayer. Anyone who had his track record would have been fired or voted out. 			
<wp:post_name><![CDATA[backstory-podcast-no-93-delta-hits-baldwin-county]]>
</wp:post_name>For those that did not get the vaccine, please think of others if not yourself.  This delta variant is a mean variant. 
<wp:post_name><![CDATA[baldwin-county-un-family-court]]>
</wp:post_name>If you are news media, why are you not reporting the actions of the Ethics Commission's Director? Or the actions of Regions Bank?Please read the first article, by Rob Holbert, Editor of Lagniappe, who broke the story. Then read the balance of articles for more details.Please share this informationHow much money has Regions Bank made from administration fees and interest? How many millions does Regions Bank have on deposit from oil revenues?Mr Albritton has used the trust to finance his children’s education, while ignoring the intent of the trust. Is it OK for the trustee to self benefit from the trust?Why did Regions Bank and the Tom Albritton not tell the citizens of Conecuh County that oil had been discovered in 2010 and 60 to 80 million dollars of oil had been pumped from beneath the county? Who paid taxes? Did the county benefit?Why has the Ethics Commission remained silent? 
<wp:post_name><![CDATA[where-is-the-media]]>
</wp:post_name>
<wp:meta_value><![CDATA[https://cdn.rippreport.com/052c14f8-missingfb.png]]></wp:meta_value>
Why is it so hard for you petty people to accept this?
<wp:post_name><![CDATA[backstory-podcast-no-94-alabamas-ethical-decay-and-delta]]>
</wp:post_name>	
39.5 Million SARS-COV-2 infected in the USA with 643,00 deaths.  The Delta variant has Gulf Coastal Hospitals are out of ICU beds and the Feds are in Foley helping out.   The Peacock Network has a new documentary series Monster in the Shadows: Inside the Beyond-Shocking Aftermath of Brittney Wood's Disappearance- about a young woman who went missing in Baldwin County- her family members were later convicted of child sexual abuse, including relatives (Another Unsolved). The Supreme Court of the Untied States in a 5-4 decision let stand a Texas abortion law that punishes participants- down to any facilitators of an abortion- after a fetal heartbeat is detected (approx. 6 weeks).  Opinions are split.  Apple withholds "child protection features" amid privacy concerns. And we ask the question: What does the Federal Trade Commission do? And the Country takes notice of Hurricane Ida (NOLA to NYC).  The Alabama Ethics Commission and the General Counsel of the Alabama State Bar responded this week to Mr. Ripp's complaints against The Executive Director of the Alabama Ethics Commission Tom Albritton for his role in the Mable Amos Scholarship Trust and the apparent benefits to his family.  And the Lagniappe Mobile Newspaper had several articles this week that you should check out.<wp:post_name><![CDATA[no-98-ethical-abortion]]>
</wp:post_name>Make sense?
The Alabama Ethics Commission forgot what the definition of Ethics's is:Ethics is based on well-founded standards of right and wrong that prescribe what humans ought to do, usually in terms of rights, obligations, benefits to society, fairness, or specific virtues. ... "Being ethical is doing what the law requires." "Ethics consists of the standards of behavior our society accepts.”Should this not be the foundation of the Ethics Commission? Or is it their position, interpreting the law in a manner that avoids accountability and rewards corruption. The Ethics Commission is aware of the scope of the complaint, however they choose to hold their noses and look the other way in the face of Mr. Albrittons, admissions.For the Ethics Commission to allow Mr. Albritton to remain Executive Director, would be tantamount to aiding and abetting political corruption in Alabama.https://rippreport.com/2021/08/06/where-is-the-media/The Ripp Report also filed a Alabama Bar complaint against Mr. Albritton, below is Mr. Albritton's responce to the Bar addressing my complaint.[embeddoc url="https://cdn.rippreport.com/2a1177a2-skm_558e2109031024011_compressed.pdf" download="all" viewer="google"]The Ripp Report will respond to the letter Mr. Albritton submitted to the Bar and post it. Mr Albritton's letter is a sad comentaryof his interpertation of has actions. His omessions of certain facts will be corrected.Mr John Bell, Regions Bank and Rick Clifton are the other two trustees, they should account f r any "scholorships"that they, or their friends, have recieved. What about employees of Regions Bank? The trust should have a forensic audit. I bet Mr Albritton is not the only trustee to use the trust as their piggy bank.https://rippreport.com/2021/07/24/striking-oil/How did Conecuh County citizens not know about the discovery of oil. Did the county get any taxes or royalities? Where was the Conecuh County Commission?<wp:post_name><![CDATA[court-of-public-opinion-2]]>
</wp:post_name>
https://www.montgomeryadvertiser.com/story/news/local/2021/09/10/cullman-al-man-dies-hospitals-full-icus-turn-away-covid/8272754002/	<wp:post_name><![CDATA[never-forget]]>
</wp:post_name>
<wp:meta_value><![CDATA[https://cdn.rippreport.com/532c8cfc-cropped-73ba15c8-911fb.jpg]]></wp:meta_value>

“The city of Fairhope bought the K-1 Center and surrounding property from the Baldwin County Board of Education in 2019 for $2.5 million. The former school campus was built in 1925 and was closed in 2011. “Thanks to Jack Burrell this has become another project like the waterfront. If Burrell is allowed to make all the decisions about K-1 future plans, you will see a wasted space and money down the drain.https://lagniappemobile.com/fairhope-state-reach-settlement-in-sewer-lawsuit/“Specific terms of the agreement require the city to develop an SSO response plan, an SSO and surface water assessment and a public notification plan, and adopt minimum standards of procedure for operation and maintenance of the wastewater treatment system. The city must provide quarterly progress reports to ADEM.”The city will also be required to put out health warnings after a sewer spill and warn any swimmers of the danger, something they omitted in the past.Thank You Tim Cant and Jack Burrell who did absolutely nothing as far as sewer infrastructure work for years. Mayor Wilson is who tackled the sewer issue and obtained millions for sewer infrastructure. She also was responsible for the 6.2 million for the Waterfront project.Mayor Sullivan and Council have to complete the work. At the rate they are going it is going to take their entire term, plus one year, to complete the projects Mayor Wilson left on the plate.This Council and Mayor with their pro development, at all costs, is changing the quality of life in Fairhope and in just a few years FAUXHOPE will just be another small town swallowed up by urban sprawl. Traffic is a good indicator of poor planning, remember that.<wp:post_name><![CDATA[fauxhope]]>
</wp:post_name>
<wp:meta_value><![CDATA[https://cdn.rippreport.com/a26dca39-cropped-839cb367-farihopesealfb.png]]></wp:meta_value>
@POTUS
<wp:post_name><![CDATA[sheriff-huey-boss-mack-secret-police]]>
</wp:post_name>
<wp:meta_value><![CDATA[https://cdn.rippreport.com/5eddbcc5-cropped-96879ecd-hmcfb.jpg]]></wp:meta_value>

<wp:post_name><![CDATA[black-cloud]]>
</wp:post_name>
<wp:meta_value><![CDATA[https://cdn.rippreport.com/74b0185a-cropped-2f4f84c1-flagfb.png]]></wp:meta_value>
	Rampant corruption.
</p><wp:post_name><![CDATA[neumann]]>
</wp:post_name>	
<wp:post_name><![CDATA[make-8-great]]>
</wp:post_name>
<wp:meta_value><![CDATA[https://cdn.rippreport.com/ec03fea9-cropped-6feeeed4-8ball.png]]></wp:meta_value>

44,700,000 SARS-COV-2 cases in the USA with 721,000 deaths. Facebook leaker has them running for the exits and The University of Alabama lost a football game this past weekend resulting in increases in domestic violence/DUI’s/and a murder.  Nick Saban is again the highest paid coach again according to the NCAA.  And UA Confidentiality Agreements are the subject of a Lagniappe article this week that you should read. The Governor signed into law a bill that would allow for the use of $400 Million in Covid Aid on $1.2 Billion for prison construction, not subject to the Public Bid Law? Baldwin Planning District 8 Fairhope/Point Clear news. Chis Elliott, Tucker "whatever your real name may be" Dorsey, Spanish Fort Mayor "Slappin" Mike McMillan, Anti-Farmers Federation Senate Candidate Mo Brooks, The de facto Governor Jo Bonner bucking for the USA president job and a whole cast of characters go round. And to drive home the power of the podcast we start with Dr. Sanjay Gupta on the JRE.<wp:post_name><![CDATA[lets-talk-about-the-bama-loss]]>
</wp:post_name>
<wp:meta_value><![CDATA[https://cdn.rippreport.com/d7205968-cropped-74e27730-bsp103fb.png]]></wp:meta_value>
			The distribution plan will rely on pediatricians, community health centers, schools and pharmacies to put parents and children at ease, rather than the mass vaccination sites used in the initial rollout for adults.The administration said it is launching a partnership with the Children's Hospital Association to work with over 100 children's hospital systems across the country to set up vaccination sites in November and through the end of the calendar year."Parents know and trust children’s hospitals to be there for their children’s medical needs, and these vaccination efforts will be no different. Pediatricians, pediatric specialists, nurses and team members will administer the vaccine to kids in trusted, family-friendly settings that serve kids every day," according to the fact sheet.The Biden administration said it has purchased enough vaccines to give shots to all the country’s 28 million children ages 5-11 years old.To that end, the Federal Emergency Management Agency (FEMA) is providing full funding to states to support vaccination operations and outreach – including setting up sites, procuring equipment and supplies to store and administer the vaccine.FEMA will also provide transportation to and from vaccination sites, and will help with public communication like public service announcements and translation services. 
<wp:post_name><![CDATA[this-is-a-test]]>
</wp:post_name>
<wp:meta_value><![CDATA[https://cdn.rippreport.com/4de2a821-cropped-ed1c1465-al_dummy.png]]></wp:meta_value>
		The news is Alabama stinks. 
<wp:post_name><![CDATA[writ-of-mandamus-update]]>
</wp:post_name>
<wp:meta_value><![CDATA[375]]></wp:meta_value>
<wp:meta_value><![CDATA[https://cdn.rippreport.com/9d90238f-cropped-dcd888e2-al_dummy2.png]]></wp:meta_value>
	Money appears stolen here. Let's hold our breath until something like justice
<wp:post_name><![CDATA[ethical-recusal]]>
</wp:post_name>	
<wp:post_name><![CDATA[happy-birthday-%f0%9f%87%ba%f0%9f%87%b8-246-years]]>
</wp:post_name>
<wp:meta_value><![CDATA[https://cdn.rippreport.com/1bed42f6-cropped-31591f92-marines-fb.png]]></wp:meta_value>
	- Paid Fauci and funded gain of function research in China (while also performing some very questionable animal activities)
<wp:post_name><![CDATA[mcsharry-madness]]>
</wp:post_name>
<wp:meta_value><![CDATA[https://cdn.rippreport.com/4626cd14-cropped-b5242a1f-mcsharrys-fairhope-alabama.png]]></wp:meta_value>
	If not repeat it until
<wp:post_name><![CDATA[perfect-puzzle]]>
</wp:post_name>
<wp:meta_value><![CDATA[https://cdn.rippreport.com/1f96e16b-cropped-04c42917-al-puzzle-fb.png]]></wp:meta_value>

<wp:post_name><![CDATA[troubled-waters]]>
</wp:post_name>
<wp:meta_value><![CDATA[Troubled Waters]]></wp:meta_value>

<wp:post_name><![CDATA[canons-no-powder]]>
</wp:post_name>
<wp:meta_value><![CDATA[https://cdn.rippreport.com/298068e5-cropped-494b5de1-cannon-rp-fb.png]]></wp:meta_value>
	Every time I hear about how "good Christian men" are, I just want to throw up.
<wp:post_name><![CDATA[january-22nd-qualifying-deadline]]>
</wp:post_name>
<wp:meta_value><![CDATA[https://cdn.rippreport.com/1cd38d31-cropped-a2cb2eeb-bsp1141.jpg]]></wp:meta_value>

<wp:post_name><![CDATA[development-chaos]]>
</wp:post_name>	wp:meta_value><![CDATA[https://cdn.rippreport.com/78b9940b-subdivisions.png]]></wp:meta_value>
Hey Ripp, can you help me count my millions??Hahahahahahahahahaahahah
<wp:post_name><![CDATA[lego-rocket-scientist]]>
</wp:post_name>
<wp:meta_value><![CDATA[https://cdn.rippreport.com/e6c1e7ac-burrell_rocket_scientist.png]]></wp:meta_value>

From Tallassee to Brookside we cover it all.  And "get-fitt'd" is the word of the week.... for that ankle monitor Baldwin County. Give it a watch and see if your favorite "black eye" politician or project gets a mention. And SARS-COV-2 is almost unavoidable at this point.<wp:post_name><![CDATA[the-black-eyes-of-alabama]]>
</wp:post_name>
<wp:meta_value><![CDATA[https://cdn.rippreport.com/ef93a5ff-cropped-0128a7cd-bsp117.jpg]]></wp:meta_value>

<wp:post_name><![CDATA[total-darkness]]>
</wp:post_name>“We are going to have a toll-free route and if you don’t want to pay the toll, you can take the toll-free route,” Burrell said. “We have done everything we can. We don’t see money coming from the federal infrastructure bill to pay for the bridge. We don’t see (additional) state money coming.”The number one reason to be suspicious of anything dealing with the bridge is, take it or leave it, Jack Burrell. His track record as a councilman has been horrible and currently he is involved in yet another controversy at the Fairhope Airport Authority.https://rippreport.com/2022/01/13/lego-rocket-scientist/Mr. Burrell being the spokesman for the I-10 project, in light of his failures, is reason enough to oppose tolls.The article also quotes, Jon Gray, a political strategist based in Mobile, are you kidding? Mr. Gray is a political strategist who can be bought, and has been, by any politician. His job is to promote B.S., and he is good at it. Why would the papers seek the advice of a biased political strategist? “ALDOT and local leaders from across Baldwin and Mobile counties have turned over every stone in Washington and Montgomery looking for additional funding, and we’ve been clear and transparent about what’s available,” he said. “The state is committed to spending at least $250 million on this project in addition to the $125 million from the federal government, which we risk losing with further delay’s.”The price tag is 2.2 billion and they have available about 500 million, so their reasoning is to toll the general public for their inability to raise enough money any other way.Consider this:David PetersonFYI: While doing some research on Toll Roads I found and article which I feel relates to the proposed I-10 Toll Bridge. If this applies in Pennsylvania then why shouldn't it apply in Alabama? (In 2007, Pennsylvania legislators passed Act 44, allowing the state to take steps toward tolling Interstate 80, running east to west through the middle of the state. Proceeds from the toll would bring in hundreds of millions of dollars each year for road repairs and public transit systems. The problem with this is states need federal authorization to add tolls to interstates. This year, the U.S. Department of Transportation rejected Pennsylvania’s third request to add tolls to I-80, leaving the state scrambling to fill a $472 million hole in its transportation budget.)“The problem with this is, states need federal authorization to add tolls to interstates.”Has Alabama got authorization to add a toll to the proposed Bay Bridge?What the citizens of Baldwin and Mobile County’s need is another NO TOLLS PETITION.Give it hell Dean Young:<wp:post_name><![CDATA[trolls-for-tolls]]>
</wp:post_name>
Daphne, Alabama 36526<wp:post_name><![CDATA[press-release]]>
</wp:post_name>
<wp:meta_value><![CDATA[https://cdn.rippreport.com/79566a8e-cropped-ded28c36-img_2547-scaled-1.jpg]]></wp:meta_value>

<wp:post_name><![CDATA[happy-days]]>
</wp:post_name>	wp:meta_value><![CDATA[https://cdn.rippreport.com/aee6942a-emojifb.png]]></wp:meta_value>

<wp:post_name><![CDATA[vote-yes-today]]>
</wp:post_name>
<wp:post_name><![CDATA[pot-calling-the-kettle-black]]>
</wp:post_name>
<wp:meta_value><![CDATA[https://cdn.rippreport.com/bd46f1bc-teapot-fb.png]]></wp:meta_value>
	He was investigated.
<wp:post_name><![CDATA[threesome]]>
</wp:post_name>	
<wp:post_name><![CDATA[bsp118]]>
</wp:post_name>
<wp:meta_value><![CDATA[https://cdn.rippreport.com/766234e2-bsp118fb.png]]></wp:meta_value>

<wp:post_name><![CDATA[deal-with-the-devil]]>
</wp:post_name>	My HOPE is for a new FAIR trial for his son. 
<wp:post_name><![CDATA[he-must-go]]>
</wp:post_name>
<wp:post_name><![CDATA[the-slap]]>
</wp:post_name>	Why is Biden not living in White House?
<wp:post_name><![CDATA[ki-yay-mother-yippee]]>
</wp:post_name>
<wp:meta_value><![CDATA[https://cdn.rippreport.com/0673b23e-bsp123.jpg]]></wp:meta_value>
<wp:post_name><![CDATA[fauxhope-roller-coaster]]>
</wp:post_name>
<wp:meta_value><![CDATA[https://cdn.rippreport.com/112d926d-fairhope-pierfb.jpg]]></wp:meta_value>

<wp:post_name><![CDATA[priorities]]>
</wp:post_name>
<wp:meta_value><![CDATA[https://cdn.rippreport.com/eb0549ff-bsp124fb.png]]></wp:meta_value>

<wp:post_name><![CDATA[innocent]]>
</wp:post_name>What about the local
<wp:post_name><![CDATA[homeland-securitys-disinformation-governance-board]]>
</wp:post_name>
<wp:meta_value><![CDATA[{"scripts":["comment-reply"]}]]></wp:meta_value>

<wp:post_name><![CDATA[bsp-128]]>
</wp:post_name>
<wp:meta_value><![CDATA[https://cdn.rippreport.com/5e09cf16-bsp-125.png]]></wp:meta_value>
	wp:meta_value><![CDATA[{"scripts":["comment-reply"]}]]></wp:meta_value>

<wp:post_name><![CDATA[shooting-yourself-in-the-foot]]>
</wp:post_name>
<wp:post_name><![CDATA[talking-heads]]>
</wp:post_name>
<wp:meta_value><![CDATA[https://cdn.rippreport.com/3e291c7f-cc-fb.png]]></wp:meta_value>

<wp:post_name><![CDATA[catalyst-eat-their-own]]>
</wp:post_name>
<wp:meta_value><![CDATA[https://rippreport.com/wp-content/uploads/69561e13-forksfb.png]]></wp:meta_value>
We TRUE Fairhopers must make sure that we assert Fairhope values on these refugees that have fled from areas that they have ruined
<wp:post_name><![CDATA[primary-election-may-24th]]>
</wp:post_name><wp:post_name><![CDATA[last-chance]]>
</wp:post_name>
<wp:meta_value><![CDATA[https://rippreport.com/wp-content/uploads/last-chance-fb.png]]></wp:meta_value>
			Obvious
<wp:post_name><![CDATA[memorial-day-3]]>
</wp:post_name>
<wp:meta_value><![CDATA[https://rippreport.com/wp-content/uploads/dc68d5f2-iwojima.png]]></wp:meta_value>

<wp:post_name><![CDATA[win-for-baldwin]]>
</wp:post_name>
<wp:meta_value><![CDATA[https://rippreport.com/wp-content/uploads/71879246-mckenziefb.png]]></wp:meta_value>
	These evil greedy SOB’s have turned Fairhope
<wp:post_name><![CDATA[fauxhope-2]]>
</wp:post_name>
<wp:meta_value><![CDATA[https://rippreport.com/wp-content/uploads/aedaaea8-farihope-sealfxfb.png]]></wp:meta_value>
	He use to say "Robert Brown from your hometown."
<wp:post_name><![CDATA[dirty-underwear]]>
</wp:post_name>
<wp:meta_value><![CDATA[https://rippreport.com/wp-content/uploads/ac6b4f12-underwearfb.png]]></wp:meta_value>
Just a few years ago Fairhope was a wonderful place to live.  Low taxes, you could swim in the bay, you could find a parking place downtown and shop at a store that served the local residents and not the tourists, low taxes, and it was a small town.	
Where is the Alabama political reporter? What about the Jeff Poor show? Why is his mic off? What about all those TV stations that brag about exposing corruption? In any other state these stories would be front page. Not in Alabama, that is why Alabama is so corrupt. The absence of press contributes to the corruption.Please read these articles, the links are open. The Attorney General, Ethics Commission and Alabama Bar represent the top shelf of corruption in Alabama.https://lagniappemobile.com/noncompliance-and-ethics-violations-lawsuit-and-examiners-report-allege-issues-at-state-bar/“The commission unanimously approved an administrative resolution of the case and forwarded [it] to the Alabama attorney general. That request has been approved by Steve Marshall, attorney general, state of Alabama,” the records stated.With Marshall punting on the possibility of any criminal investigation of McCallum’s behavior, the Ethics Commission meted out fines for his various transgressions.”https://lagniappemobile.com/alabamas-recipe-for-corruption/“If I had to bake an “Alabama Corruption Cake” the recipe would probably go something like this: 2 parts shiftless opportunists, 2 parts complicit appointed boards and agencies, 1 part disinterested Attorney General’s Office, 1 part ineffective Ethics Commission and 2 pinches of one-party rule. Blend thoroughly, bake for 200 years and ice generously with inept and partisan press coverage. Serves 5 million.Needless to say, all of this is made worse by the fact that the State Bar is run by lawyers who are supposed to know and follow the law. McCallum’s behavior not only appears to have been swept under the rug by the attorney general (lawyer), Ethics Commission (run by a lawyer) and the State Bar (lots of lawyers), he received zero punishment from the State Bar.”https://rippreport.com/2022/07/01/dirty-underwear/“The Ethics Commission’s Executive Director, Tom Albritton, has got a pass from the Ethics Commission, Alabama Bar and the Attorney General. The only recourse for any justice is to file a civil suit against Mr Albrittion the trustees and the bank. This is blatant in your face corruption, at the highest level of our state’s government.”https://lagniappemobile.com/self-dealing-ethics-directors-kids-tuition-paid-from-trust-he-oversees/“Albritton was confirmed by the State Senate as executive director of the Alabama Ethics Commission in March 2015, and that same year, two of his children received $15,000 scholarships to the University of Texas from the trust, according to 990 records. Overall, scholarships to Albritton’s children totaled $105,000 between 2014 and 2018, which is the last year for which the trust’s 990s are available, so it is possible there was more scholarship money distributed to them.”<wp:post_name><![CDATA[top-shelf-corruption]]>
</wp:post_name>
<wp:meta_value><![CDATA[https://rippreport.com/wp-content/uploads/6120761f-altopfb.png]]></wp:meta_value>

<wp:post_name><![CDATA[water]]>
</wp:post_name>
<wp:post_name><![CDATA[elephants-in-alabama]]>
</wp:post_name>	wp:meta_value><![CDATA[https://rippreport.com/wp-content/uploads/85550581-alel.png]]></wp:meta_value>

The suit, filed in Montgomery County Circuit Court, alleges a scheme between Regions Bank and its representative on the Mabel Amos Charitable Trust, John Bell, and Albritton and his former law partner Rick Clifton. Albritton and Clifton have served as two of the three board members for the trust since its inception after Amos’ death in 1999.”It took a civil lawsuit, not Ethics complaints, Bar Complaints or letters to the Attorney General, to seek any level of justice. The allegations involved show how these “respected men” stole from children for their own personal benefit. They did this by “self dealing” the trust.It is going to be very enlightening when the case reaches the discovery point. Who did the “Trust” give scholarships too? We already know that lawyers in charge of the trust had a feeding frenzy awarding themselves, and connected friends, hundreds of thousands of dollars.<Think about that! The Bank and the Trustees put themselves first and those deserving kids who qualified for scholarships, last.>“Scholarships to Albritton’s daughter were listed by name one year and afterward, delineated by a notation that said, “Scholarship for Board Member Daughter.” Overall, Albritton’s son and daughter received at least $120,000 in scholarship money from the trust. While the lawsuit alleges other board members received scholarship money for their children, Lagniappe has not been able to verify that.Albritton has denied wrongdoing, claiming he was not involved in “self-dealing” because he abstained from voting for the scholarships for his children. Still, the question of why Regions was allowed to massively increase its fees — $1.2 million taken between 2002 and 2020 — is one raised in the lawsuit.”I would suggest that you consider any other bank, than REGIONS“Lagniappe was also able to verify that one of Albritton’s former law partners, current Covington County Circuit Court Judge Ben Bowden, has a child who was awarded scholarships to Southern Methodist University (SMU) totaling $45,000 between 2014 and 2017.”The executive director of the Ethics Commission, Tom Albritton, should be fired immediately from the so called Ethics Commission. He has paid 120,000 to the University of TEXAS, not Alabama, for his two children’s education.In any other state this would be front page news for weeks. Instead we see those involved using the very agencies intended on preventing such a scheme, to their advantage.This is a line in the sand. If those responsible are allowed to keep their ill begotten gains, and jobs, then it will be proof positive that Alabama is the most corrupt state in the United States.<wp:post_name><![CDATA[line-in-the-sand]]>
</wp:post_name>
<wp:post_name><![CDATA[bsp-131]]>
</wp:post_name>No white collar crimes or political corruption cases submitted to the A.G.’s office, see the light of day.That is why Alabama politics is so corrupt. The Politicians that are corrupt, know Marshall has their backs.This is the letter the Attorney General sent me back about a complaint, I filed with his office related to the Ethics Director Tom Albritton: Please note that the letter re: Complaint, no name? The letter is not signed either. Best yet you got to love the sentence “WE cannot, however, disclose to you any decision about your complaint”--ALABAMA SHUFFLEhttps://www.alreporter.com/2022/07/27/opinion-please-pay-attention-to-steve-marshall/“Here’s what that’s gotten you: An AG who files, or signs onto, frivolous lawsuits that mean nothing and usually go nowhere, while ignoring cases that do matter to Alabamians – cases that could protect the citizens of this state.”Attorney General Marshall did the Alabama Shuffle when the complaint hit his desk related to the Ethics Executive Director Tom Albritton.https://rippreport.com/2022/07/14/elephants-in-alabama/The Attorney General has only covered the backs of the Bar and Ethics, no criminal charges have been filed.Now a civil lawsuit has been filed, outlining the charges against the Ethics Director. Will this finally wake up the press ? Maybe, however The Ripp Report is going to disseminate the articles and facts for you. If this is not clear evidence of how corrupt Alabama is, what is? No state agency, or our Governor have taken any action. Alabama will remain the most corrupt state and laughing stock of the United States, if such blatant corruption is ignored.
<wp:post_name><![CDATA[alabama-shuffle]]>
</wp:post_name>No conviction.
<wp:post_name><![CDATA[liars-bridge]]>
</wp:post_name>
<wp:meta_value><![CDATA[https://rippreport.com/wp-content/uploads/76bce144-burell-fairhope-al-fb.png]]></wp:meta_value>
	We pay registration fees. With all this they want us to pay a toll?
Mister Ripp Jack is asking Fairhopers to not flush after peeing onky for pooping.	wp:post_name><![CDATA[the-mcsharry-will-out]]>
</wp:post_name>
<wp:post_name><![CDATA[boycott-mcsharry]]>
</wp:post_name>HELLO&gt;Beuller?
<wp:post_name><![CDATA[stinking-ticking-time-bomb]]>
</wp:post_name>			Lies.
<wp:post_name><![CDATA[schools-and-taxes]]>
</wp:post_name>
<wp:meta_value><![CDATA[https://rippreport.com/wp-content/uploads/4793360f-school-admin-fb.png]]></wp:meta_value>

<wp:post_name><![CDATA[get-out-of-jail-card]]>
</wp:post_name>
<wp:meta_value><![CDATA[https://rippreport.com/wp-content/uploads/750ffe1b-get_out_of_jail_free-fb.png]]></wp:meta_value>

<wp:post_name><![CDATA[mouthpiece]]>
</wp:post_name>
<wp:meta_value><![CDATA[https://rippreport.com/wp-content/uploads/63ffaeaa-jack-burrell-toll-bridge-mobile.png]]></wp:meta_value>
<wp:meta_value><![CDATA[682]]></wp:meta_value>

<wp:post_name><![CDATA[cameras]]>
</wp:post_name>Barf
<wp:post_name><![CDATA[fly-creek-mud]]>
</wp:post_name>
<wp:post_name><![CDATA[carolyn-amick]]>
</wp:post_name>
<wp:meta_value><![CDATA[https://rippreport.com/wp-content/uploads/1f561996-carolyn-amick-rrfb.png]]></wp:meta_value>

<wp:post_name><![CDATA[lethal-force]]>
</wp:post_name>
<wp:meta_value><![CDATA[https://rippreport.com/wp-content/uploads/173d5817-cdfb.png]]></wp:meta_value>
<wp:post_name><![CDATA[9-11]]>
</wp:post_name><style>
.entry-meta-cats {display:none}<wp:post_name><![CDATA[celebration-of-life]]>
</wp:post_name>	
<wp:post_name><![CDATA[the-law-enforcement-narrative]]>
</wp:post_name>
<wp:post_name><![CDATA[biased-investigation]]>
</wp:post_name>
<wp:meta_value><![CDATA[https://rippreport.com/wp-content/uploads/658cf2e4-cropped-bf2498f4-baldwin-county-sherrifs-officefb.png]]></wp:meta_value>

<wp:post_name><![CDATA[wrongful-conviction]]>
</wp:post_name>			He must be distracted 
Be sure to read this article very carefully and you will see red flags have been hanging over the Baldwin County Sheriff’s Office and BCSCU, for a number of years.The Rev. Sam White, who graduated high school with French’s older sister, Tamara, spoke during the event on behalf of the family and said there needs to be transparency in the investigation.“‘Once Mr. French exited the vehicle, he would not comply with the officer’s instructions,’” said White, reading from the official report. “Some things already aren’t adding up for me. What instructions? He wasn’t under arrest. He wasn’t being held in custody. It seems like the community needs some answers.”Rumors is all the public has because Baldwin County Major Crimes Unit, BCMCU, the County Commission and the City of bay Minette, Mayor and Council have all swallowed their tongue. They are solely responsible for the lack of information, misinformation and rumors circulating throughout Baldwin County.BCMCU consists of Bay Minette Police Chief Al Tolbert, who is the current chairman, Robertsdale Police Chief Brad Kendrick, Sheriff Huey “Hoss” Mack of the Baldwin County Sheriff’s Office (BCSO), Gulf Shores Police Chief Edward Delmore, Daphne Police Chief David Carpenter and Foley Police Chief Thurston Bullock. The agency is tasked with reviewing the actions of officers working for its member organizations.BCMCU has no credibility. They are investigating themselves and Chief Tolbert of Bay Minette is the Chairman? It is prosperous to believe BCMCU could conduct an unbiased investigation of their own members.https://rippreport.com/2022/09/23/biased-investigation/Rumors say the officer who shot O. J. French was Brandon Thompson. Rumors say he was previously fired by the City of Bay Minette and other police forces. Rumors say The alleged rumored officer actually stopped Mr French early in the day. Rumors say Police Chief Tolbert has also been fired from Bay Minette. Rumors say Mayor Wills wants any investigation sealed from the public. Rumors say that there are many deputies of the Sheriff Department that see the BCMCU as a way to cover up actions of a few bad officers. Rumors say Mr. French was shot in the back. Rumors say that the Bay Minette police department was well aware Mr French suffered with diagnosed mental health issues. Rumors say that elected officials plan to remain silent and not to question the actions of the BCMCU, the sheriff or Police Chief Tolbert. Rumors say the officer was back on duty with a weapon within several weeks of the shooting. Rumors say the camera footage will never be provided to the public. Rumors say the grand Jury is flawed by being secret, that often evidence is left out or the information provided by the police is questionable. Rumors say the Grand Jury is just another vehicle the BCSCU uses to cover up officer malfeasance.Mr French is the 9th loss of life in Baldwin County where the BCMCU has investigated themselves. The first 8 found no police at fault and camera footage was withheld from the public..In the case of Johnthan Victor on April 2021 Judge William Cassady DENIED Hunady, the sheriff deputy who shot Victor four times, and sheriff Mack qualified immunity. The Judges ruling is on appeal by the Baldwin County Sheriff Office. The sheriff provided facts about the case that were untrue. Victor was unarmed and shot from 7 yards.Victor like French had issues with mental health. Sheriff Mack said In open court that the sheriff dept did not have any special training for handling cases involving persons with issues of mental health, How in the hell is that possible?The Alabama Supreme Court on Friday ruled against a Mobile media outlet seeking law enforcement files related to a fatal police shooting, sparking a fervent dissent from the court's own chief justice regarding the state's public records law.The court upheld a Baldwin County ruling in the case, in which Lagniappe Mobile sued for investigative records from the Baldwin County Sheriff’s Office related to the 2017 shooting of motorist Jonathan Victor. The high court ruled the records Lagniappe sought, including dash and body camera footage from the shooting, are all exempted from open records law due to their "investigative" nature, even though the investigation in the shooting has been closed.Sheriff Hoss Mack told a County Commissioners that he needed 600,000.00 of taxpayer money for cameras. The cameras would provide transparency and accountability to the general public and police. That has turned out to be total bullsh--, he, and BCSCU has refused to share any footage involving any incident.Another disturbing fact is that the sheriff office is well known for putting out misleading or false information surrounding loss of life cases by sheriff officers.It should be noted that the vast majority of police do their job honorable however 1 to 3% can be very problematic. A common practice in Baldwin County is police officers being fired from one municipality then being hired by another municipality. It is often the case that the officer in question, like the French case, has been fired by a previous law enforcement job. Of course that is just a rumor, for right now.For more on this case please listen to our podcast:<wp:post_name><![CDATA[rumors]]>
</wp:post_name>
<wp:meta_value><![CDATA[https://rippreport.com/wp-content/uploads/1bec3e30-telephonefb.png]]></wp:meta_value>
<wp:post_name><![CDATA[holding-our-breath]]>
</wp:post_name>
<wp:post_name><![CDATA[alabama-black-hole]]>
</wp:post_name>
<wp:meta_value><![CDATA[https://rippreport.com/wp-content/uploads/f1333097-blackhole-al-fb.png]]></wp:meta_value>

<wp:post_name><![CDATA[this-is-the-new-logo-for-fairhope]]>
</wp:post_name>Nohope.
<wp:post_name><![CDATA[veterans-day-in-alabama]]>
</wp:post_name>
<wp:meta_value><![CDATA[https://rippreport.com/wp-content/uploads/a682bebe-vetsfb.png]]></wp:meta_value>

<wp:post_name><![CDATA[delight]]>
</wp:post_name>
<wp:meta_value><![CDATA[https://rippreport.com/wp-content/uploads/0f46dbbd-catalystvotefb.png]]></wp:meta_value>
Big law firm with law offices all over the state.
<wp:post_name><![CDATA[marine-corp-birthday]]>
</wp:post_name>wp:meta_value><![CDATA[https://rippreport.com/wp-content/uploads/567c9adf-veteransday.png]]></wp:meta_value>
<wp:meta_value><![CDATA[veterans-day-2]]></wp:meta_value>
<wp:post_name><![CDATA[belize-vacation-another-world]]>
</wp:post_name>
<wp:post_name><![CDATA[wp-global-styles-rippreport]]>
</wp:post_name>			
<wp:post_name><![CDATA[bay%f0%9f%90%96minette]]>
</wp:post_name>
<wp:post_name><![CDATA[sunday-sermon]]>
</wp:post_name>
<wp:meta_value><![CDATA[https://rippreport.com/wp-content/uploads/aa80aabe-sermon.png]]></wp:meta_value>

<wp:post_name><![CDATA[merry-christmas-%f0%9f%8e%85]]>
</wp:post_name>
Good Riddance 2022.  The Baldwin County Legislative Delegation is renting office space to accommodate their growing family. The Mayor of Bay Minette Robert A Bob Wills just so happens to have an available building.  The County is required to provide space for the Delegation for their local office and in fact own many offices in Bay Minette at this time, Mr. Ripp has issues with this transaction.  No one at the County or State Level "GIVES A  DAMN".  We break down the players and perps related to the NPR Expose exposing that the Yellow Hammer News, Alabama Political Reporter, ECT, are all part of the Matrix LLC Network and it is indeed, fake news in some cases (which calls your entire credibility into question). Some of them are on your talk radio every day. And guess who their guests are? Pitman, Elliott, Mack. After numerous complaints and a lawsuit, AG Steve Marshall woke from his cryo-sleep and has joined the Mable Amos Trust lawsuit stating " The State of Alabama has an interest in the case".  Tom Albritton the Executive Director of the Alabama Ethics Commission and is also a Trustee of the Amos Trust where he is accused of self dealing.  He also indicted former Jefferson County Constable Johnathan Barbee of several felonies even though we are aware that he was just cleared by a 3-Judge Special Ethics Panel.  And finally we tell you about the murder of Blount County Circuit Judge Steven King, or of his reputation rather.<wp:post_name><![CDATA[bonum-est-faciet-2022]]>
</wp:post_name>wp:post_name><![CDATA[happy-new-year-%f0%9f%8e%89]]>
</wp:post_name><wp:post_name><![CDATA[mcsharrys-old-flower-handshake]]>
</wp:post_name>
<wp:meta_value><![CDATA[https://rippreport.com/wp-content/uploads/d0ef3139-cropped-3aa98319-lucky-charms.png]]></wp:meta_value>

<wp:post_name><![CDATA[stephen-nodine]]>
</wp:post_name>
<wp:post_name><![CDATA[go-to-hell-ethics]]>
</wp:post_name>
<wp:meta_value><![CDATA[https://rippreport.com/wp-content/uploads/bf71d842-scale-flames.png]]></wp:meta_value>
Help me out.  
<wp:post_name><![CDATA[balloonapaloosa]]>
</wp:post_name>
<wp:meta_value><![CDATA[https://rippreport.com/wp-content/uploads/7a00d29c-balloonapaloosa.png]]></wp:meta_value>
<wp:post_name><![CDATA[alabamas-ethics-director-should-resign]]>
</wp:post_name>	
<wp:post_name><![CDATA[cover-up]]>
</wp:post_name>